{"text":"Shooting Rampage Results In 'Mass Casualties' At Orlando Gay Nightclub. ORLANDO, Fla., June 12 (Reuters) - A gunman killed at least 20 people and injured 42 others in a crowded gay nightclub in","label":[[29,45,"ORG"],[49,70,"ORG"],[72,79,"GPE"],[81,85,"GPE"],[87,94,"DATE"],[96,103,"ORG"],[123,134,"CARDINAL"],[154,156,"CARDINAL"]]}
{"text":"Donald Trump Lashes Out At CNN, ABC Over Reporting Errors. The president criticized the \"fake news media\" during a Florida rally.","label":[[0,19,"PERSON"],[27,30,"ORG"],[32,35,"ORG"],[41,57,"ORG"],[115,122,"GPE"]]}
{"text":"Model Kate Moss Walks Louis Vuitton RTW Fall 2013. Golden girl model Kate Moss wowed in her usual chic way as she walked the Louis Vuitton Ready-To-Wear Fall Collection 2013 fashion show. Moss continues to give us a close look at her ability to inspire while wearing all things gorgeous. Yes, absolutely Louis Vuitton gorgeous.","label":[[0,39,"PERSON"],[69,73,"PERSON"],[121,138,"ORG"],[304,317,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"7 Ways Single Moms Cope With Loneliness. “Am I the only single mom feeling lonely out there?” asks Kelly B. Her words underscore a common plight for Circle of Moms","label":[[0,1,"CARDINAL"],[99,107,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"Sen. Sherrod Brown: Steve Bannon 'Is A White Supremacist'. Echoing comments by Rep. Frederica Wilson, he cites \"studies\" that say allies of white supremacists are \"sprinkled around the White House.\"","label":[[5,18,"PERSON"],[20,34,"PERSON"],[84,100,"PERSON"],[181,196,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"eBay Bans Confederate Flags. The website called it a \"symbol of divisiveness and racism.\"","label":[[0,4,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"Derek Jeter Fakes Out Opponent To Start Double Play. ","label":[[0,17,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"Brazilian Squatters Offer Shelter From Anti-LGBTQ Violence. “It’s not my fault that I live in a society with an empty heart and mind.”","label":[[0,9,"NORP"]]}
{"text":"10 Cities That Could Run Out Of Water - Weather.com. Securing access to plentiful, renewable sources of fresh water is among the biggest struggles large cities around the world","label":[[0,2,"CARDINAL"]]}
{"text":"North Carolina Ball Team Threw Retirement Party For Its Bat Dog. Miss Babe Ruth will retire after appearing in 649 consecutive games.","label":[[0,47,"GPE"],[70,79,"PERSON"],[111,114,"CARDINAL"]]}
{"text":"Morocco's Role in Supporting Human Development in Africa. Sustainable development in the African south is inextricable from social issues. The continent's talented populations and vast youth demographic have the potential to make the continent a global powerhouse -- but not unless present-day ills are healed.","label":[[0,7,"GPE"],[10,14,"GPE"],[50,56,"LOC"],[89,96,"NORP"]]}
{"text":"Trevor Noah Explains Why Donald Trump Is Really 'The Dress'. \"We're all trying to figure out what the hell it is.\"","label":[[25,40,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"Another Dreamer Sues In Federal Court To Help Millions Get Expanded Immigration Relief. A young undocumented student from Chicago hopes to achieve what the Supreme Court couldn't.","label":[[122,129,"GPE"],[152,169,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"Marco Rubio: 'I Do' Think I'm Ready To Be President. ","label":[[0,12,"PERSON"],[30,41,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"Japanese Gymnast Racks Up A $5,000 Pokémon Go Bill In Rio. Which is particularly strange given that there are no Pokémon in Rio.","label":[[0,8,"NORP"],[29,34,"MONEY"],[124,127,"GPE"]]}
{"text":"Elizabeth Warren To FBI: I Can Think Of Some Other Investigations You Should Release. If the FBI is suddenly releasing information about investigations, Warren says, why not those investigations into the 2008 financial crisis?","label":[[0,16,"PERSON"],[20,23,"ORG"],[93,96,"ORG"],[153,159,"GPE"],[204,208,"CARDINAL"]]}
{"text":"Coal State Senators Look To Block Obama's Climate Rules. \"There's a war on coal in America,\" says Mitch McConnell, \"and the leader is the president of the United States.\"","label":[[83,90,"GPE"],[98,113,"PERSON"],[151,168,"GPE"]]}
{"text":"Living the Good Life: 35 Profound Quotes From the \"Seven Sages of Greece\". There are many things for which we owe the Greeks: democracy, geometry, the marathon. Not to mention souvlaki, moussaka and baklava. But arguably the most valuable asset to any person: wisdom.","label":[[22,24,"CARDINAL"],[66,72,"GPE"],[118,124,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"Have Fun Without the Stress This Holiday Season. In real life, unless you have a personal event planner or live in the Land of Oz, it's difficult, stressful and maybe even impossible to pull off the perfect holiday. Here are a few ways to calm your nerves and your expectations during the \"most wonderful time of the year.\"","label":[[115,129,"GPE"],[313,321,"DATE"]]}
{"text":"Give Your Father The Gift Of Cocktails. This weekend, honor your pops by making him a delicious drink. Here are a few of our favorites. You can thank us later. Cheers!","label":[[40,52,"DATE"]]}
{"text":"Rudy Giuliani Wanted To Move On From The Trump Tape. Chuck Todd Wouldn't Let Him.. The \"Meet the Press\" host seems to be just as sickened by Trump as everyone else.","label":[[0,13,"PERSON"],[53,63,"PERSON"],[83,102,"WORK_OF_ART"]]}
{"text":"Nick Cannon On Trump: 'I Like My Racism Served Right To My Face'. The entertainer had some choice words about the state of America now.","label":[[0,11,"PERSON"],[123,130,"GPE"]]}
{"text":"Pete Carroll Explains Why Your Workplace Should Encourage Teamwork. \"It's the feeling that everyone brings to the workplace that will bring out their best. They'll work harder,\" the Seahawks coach says.","label":[[0,21,"PERSON"],[182,190,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"This Is Even Bigger Than Brock: What We Can All Do to Dismantle Rape Culture. Change is possible and within each of us. When \"Emily\"--and then BuzzFeed--told her story, she permanently reshaped the public conversation, making the norms that enable this kind of violence impossible to ignore. The students who stopped the attack are role models to each of us.","label":[[143,151,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"NFL Investigating Jameis Winston After Uber Driver Says The Quarterback Groped Her. The Tampa Bay player previously faced a civil suit over rape allegations.","label":[[0,3,"ORG"],[18,50,"PERSON"],[56,82,"PERSON"],[88,97,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"Ladies Who Like To Drink Owe A Little Thanks To Prohibition. To celebrate the 82nd anniversary of its repeal, the feminist upside of prohibition.","label":[[78,82,"ORDINAL"]]}
{"text":"Croatian Gay Rights Activists Protest Ahead Of Marriage Equality Referendum. In May, the Church-backed In the Name of the Family group collected over 700,000 signatures seeking a nationwide vote on","label":[[0,64,"ORG"],[80,83,"DATE"],[89,95,"ORG"],[122,128,"PRODUCT"]]}
{"text":"The Best Holiday Gifts You Can Buy At The Drugstore (Yes, Really). We've all been there: Holiday season rolls around and you either don't have time to get everyone on your list a gift or you","label":[[89,103,"DATE"]]}
{"text":"Trump’s Zig-Zagging On Health Care Back To Zig. For Now.. The president lurches from “repeal it now” to “who cares, it’s failing.”","label":[[0,7,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"Upstate New York: Good Food Is A Small Town Value. We usually sit under the Obama HOPE poster, listen to the other regulars talk at the bar, anticipate the food and feel the week fall away.","label":[[8,16,"GPE"],[170,183,"DATE"]]}
{"text":"Glenn Greenwald Reacts To Pulitzer Prize. ","label":[[0,22,"PERSON"],[26,40,"WORK_OF_ART"]]}
{"text":"12 Beers Brewed With Meat, Donuts, and Other Crazy Ingredients. You might have expanded your drinking palate beyond Crazy Stallion since you finished college.","label":[[0,2,"CARDINAL"],[116,130,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"The Beauty And Splendor Of Being A Slut. This originally appeared on VICE US It was when I read an opinion piece by a British writer Dylan Jones that I learned I","label":[[4,39,"WORK_OF_ART"],[74,76,"GPE"],[118,125,"NORP"],[133,144,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"Prenuptial Agreements: Are They Necessary? Two Legal Experts Debate. News reports of celebrity splits often center around one big question: Does the divorcing couple have a prenup? And what","label":[[43,46,"CARDINAL"],[122,125,"CARDINAL"]]}
{"text":"Pinterest Now Analyzing Pay For Discrimination Against Women. Big companies have been doing this for years, and now startups are too.","label":[[14,60,"ORG"],[101,106,"DATE"]]}
{"text":"Rainbow Fashion Week: Queer Style With a Social Responsibility Message. Rainbow Fashion Week recently returned to NYC, kicking off Manhattan's Pride events with eight days of queer style. RFW founder, E. Jaguar Beckford (aka Jag), was intentional about producing a style event that was inclusive and representative of the LGBTQ community's values.","label":[[0,20,"ORG"],[72,92,"ORG"],[114,117,"ORG"],[131,140,"GPE"],[143,148,"PRODUCT"],[161,171,"DATE"],[201,219,"PERSON"],[225,228,"PERSON"],[322,327,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"Pro Wrestler's Penis Takedown Just Got Bigger. Below the belt, beyond the pale","label":[[0,14,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"32 Truths I've Learned By My 32nd Birthday. I felt so adult in my mid 20s, which I'm grateful for because I'm sure it propelled me to where I am today. But at 32, I can wholeheartedly say I feel much freer and younger in mind, body and spirit.","label":[[0,2,"CARDINAL"],[29,33,"ORDINAL"],[63,73,"DATE"],[145,150,"DATE"],[159,161,"DATE"]]}
{"text":"Negative Self-Talk: 9 Ways To Silence Your Inner Critic. 3. Ask Yourself If You're Really So Guilty Let's say in a meeting you blurt out that your Spanx are too tight. You think","label":[[20,21,"CARDINAL"],[57,58,"CARDINAL"],[147,152,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"Carly Fiorina Sharpened Political Edges In 2010 Senate Bid. Her unsuccessful campaign against Barbara Boxer in California served as a preview of the GOP contender's acerbic style on the 2016 trail.","label":[[0,39,"ORG"],[43,47,"DATE"],[48,54,"ORG"],[94,107,"PERSON"],[111,121,"GPE"],[149,152,"ORG"],[186,190,"DATE"]]}
{"text":"3 Mistakes Most People Make When Creating Their Vision Board. Now give the same bag of random items to some adults and they won't know what to do. They will begin searching the bag for instructions. Looking to see what should be done or how. There is no zest, no test just where are the instruction so I can do this the \"right way.\"","label":[[0,1,"CARDINAL"]]}
{"text":"Not All Hurricanes Are Equal. I am hardly a hurricane expert, though I did write a book about The Great Hurricane: 1938 (Atlantic Monthly Press) in 2005","label":[[94,119,"WORK_OF_ART"],[121,143,"ORG"],[148,152,"DATE"]]}
{"text":"Miami-Dade County Bans Styrofoam From Parks, Beaches. A state bill, however, prevented lawmakers from passing more comprehensive legislation.","label":[[0,17,"GPE"]]}
{"text":"3 Bad Habits That Are Hurting Your Hair... And How To Break Them. 3. Overdrying your hair. Using heat-styling tools like a blow dryer and flat iron on color or chemical-treated hair furthers","label":[[66,67,"CARDINAL"]]}
{"text":"The Internet Couldn't Get Enough Of Gucci Mane And Keyshia Ka'oir's Luxurious Wedding. Congrats to the Wopsters! ❤️","label":[[51,67,"PERSON"],[68,85,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"Half-Truths Keep You Stuck. Being polite often means not communicating how we really feel. We swallow the truth to keep our jobs, our friends and to maintain the peace in the family. It's likely better that way, but when it comes to figuring out next career and life moves, half-truths will keep you stuck.","label":[[274,278,"CARDINAL"]]}
{"text":"Mr. Trump, 17 Presidents Before You Protected Our National Parks. Will You?. The focus on reducing our public lands sent me looking to see what former presidents have done.","label":[[4,9,"PERSON"],[11,13,"CARDINAL"]]}
{"text":"Here's Evidence Floyd Mayweather And Conor McGregor Actually Love Each Other. We knew it!","label":[[16,32,"PERSON"],[37,60,"PERSON"],[61,76,"WORK_OF_ART"]]}
{"text":"25-Year-Old Mom Gives Birth To Baby From Embryo Frozen In 1992. \"Do you realize I'm only 25? This embryo and I could have been best friends,\" the mother says.","label":[[0,11,"DATE"],[58,62,"DATE"]]}
{"text":"White House Official Gives Lip Service To Puerto Rican Debt Relief But Offers No New Deal. Existing legislation is enough to reduce the island’s obligations, said Mick Mulvaney.","label":[[0,11,"ORG"],[163,176,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"How The Mizzou Protests Demonstrate The Power Of College Athletes. \"All of it boils down to athletes standing up.\"","label":[[36,65,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"Holy Knockoff, Batman! Man Busted For Throwing 'Batarang' At Cops. The \"Batman-style throwing star” was found embedded in the front of a Seattle police SUV following a chase, authorities said.","label":[[0,13,"PERSON"],[15,21,"PERSON"],[72,78,"WORK_OF_ART"],[137,144,"GPE"]]}
{"text":"The Export-Import Bank Provision That Could Be A Problem In Government Funding Negotiations. A provision to allow the Export-Import Bank to make loans above $10 million could provide lawmakers with some last-minute fireworks.","label":[[0,91,"ORG"],[114,136,"ORG"],[151,168,"MONEY"],[203,214,"TIME"]]}
{"text":"Inequality, Political Education And Lilla's Liberalism. Professors and students highlighting our differences do so to ensure we don't repeat the mistakes of the past.","label":[[0,10,"ORG"],[36,41,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"Coffee Could Help Cirrhosis Patients Live Longer. Dr. Koh and team were interested in conducting this research because some studies have suggested coffee may be beneficial","label":[[54,57,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"More Than Half Of Doctors Support National Legalization Of Marijuana, Survey Shows. Doctors in certain specialties seemed to better acknowledge the benefits of medical marijuana than others. Eighty-two percent","label":[[0,14,"CARDINAL"],[191,209,"PERCENT"]]}
{"text":"Assad's Forces Take 'Capital Of Revolution'. ","label":[[0,43,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"Pennsylvania Lawmaker Slammed As 'Lying Homosexual' By Colleague. Daryl Metcalfe's war of words with fellow state Rep. Brian Sims has been ongoing for years.","label":[[0,29,"ORG"],[66,82,"PERSON"],[119,129,"PERSON"],[151,156,"DATE"]]}
{"text":"That Chicken Nugget Tweet Is On Course To Become The Most Retweeted Of All Time. Ellen DeGeneres may be about to lose her crown.","label":[[81,96,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"Requiem for a Cinematic Heavyweight: Adieu Abu Dhabi Film Festival. Just a few days before this year's Festival de Cannes, those of us who watch, love and write about Arab cinema received a press release from Abu Dhabi that seemed like just another announcement.","label":[[68,83,"DATE"],[96,100,"DATE"],[103,121,"PERSON"],[167,171,"NORP"],[209,218,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"A World of Kindness: This Week in Daily Giving. I have the privilege of making seed grants to social change leaders around the world. Here are the extraordinary people and projects that our community of givers supported this week.","label":[[21,30,"DATE"],[34,46,"WORK_OF_ART"],[220,229,"DATE"]]}
{"text":"Kim Kardashian's 11 Best Outfits Of 2015. Merry Kim-Mas!","label":[[0,16,"PERSON"],[17,19,"CARDINAL"],[20,40,"EVENT"],[42,55,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"Why I Question Every New Breast-Is-Best Finding These Days. Celiac disease is on the rise, quadrupling in the United States over the last 50 years. Breastfeeding, too, is on the rise, tripling here during this same time period. Interestingly, new reports boast that breast milk may prevent celiac disease. So how could this be true?","label":[[48,58,"DATE"],[106,123,"GPE"],[129,146,"DATE"]]}
{"text":"Wedding Program Hilariously Explains The Day's Events. See the top 13 wedding trends of 2013 in the slideshow below. Check out more creative wedding programs here. Timtasticc's","label":[[41,44,"DATE"],[67,69,"CARDINAL"],[88,92,"CARDINAL"]]}
{"text":"Environmental Groups Sue White House After Trump Takes Axe To National Monuments. “President Trump has perpetrated a terrible violation of America’s public lands.\"","label":[[25,36,"ORG"],[43,80,"PERSON"],[93,98,"PERSON"],[139,146,"GPE"]]}
{"text":"Batter Up! Take a Swing at Spring Training in Florida. Florida invented spring training and hosted the first integrated baseball game. Here's an introduction to the Florida cities that take you out to the ballgames.","label":[[46,53,"GPE"],[55,62,"GPE"],[165,172,"GPE"]]}
{"text":"Summit Entertainment Releases Several Clips From 'The Legend Of Hercules'. Summit Entertainment has released four clips from their upcoming film, \"The Legend of Hercules.\" Not to be confused with","label":[[50,73,"WORK_OF_ART"],[75,95,"ORG"],[109,113,"CARDINAL"],[147,169,"WORK_OF_ART"]]}
{"text":"Hanukkah & Christmas: Can We Celebrate Both?. For parents of different faiths, December often brings holiday challenges. For divorced parents with joint custody, these challenges can be amplified.","label":[[0,20,"ORG"],[79,87,"DATE"]]}
{"text":"Boston Families Struggle With Lockdown. \"I said, 'Look, I can tell you, with certainty, that we're safe in our house, but I'm not going to lie to you about the fact","label":[[0,38,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"365 Invocations to Create an Extraordinary Life, Week 13. \"What does freedom mean to me?\" is one of the most important question you will ever ask yourself.  And, of course, as with any important question, you have to journey deep inside in order to find out what holds the truth for you.","label":[[49,56,"DATE"]]}
{"text":"Theranos Voids Two Years of Edison Blood-Test Results. Company led by Elizabeth Holmes withdraws all Edison results from 2014 and 2015, issues tens of thousands of corrected blood","label":[[15,24,"DATE"],[28,53,"ORG"],[70,86,"PERSON"],[101,107,"ORG"],[121,125,"DATE"],[130,134,"DATE"],[143,160,"CARDINAL"]]}
{"text":"A Love Letter to LGBT Progress. I doubt the people who took a stand on a hot summer evening at the Stonewall Inn knew their acts of defiance would usher in a new era of LGBT rights. Oh how I wish we could go back to that day in 1969 to tell all those people what was ahead.","label":[[2,13,"WORK_OF_ART"],[17,30,"ORG"],[77,91,"TIME"],[95,112,"FAC"],[228,232,"DATE"]]}
{"text":"Camila Cabello Recognizes Dreamers Ahead Of U2's Performance By Statue Of Liberty. “Tonight, in this room full of dreamers, we remember that this country was built by dreamers, for dreamers, chasing the American dream.\"","label":[[0,40,"ORG"],[84,91,"TIME"],[203,211,"NORP"]]}
{"text":"I On Exceptional Living -- Cindy Crawford: Charity Ambassador. It is Cindy's sense of priorities and work-life balance that makes her an example of truly exceptional living. The happily married mother of two has stated that if she must choose between her family and career, she chooses family--without hesitation.","label":[[69,74,"PERSON"],[204,207,"CARDINAL"]]}
{"text":"War Against Muslims Post 9\/11?. 9\/11 has changed the life of Muslims substantially. Almost overnight, they became the target of media-hype, various \"anti-terror\" efforts, religious intolerance and hate crimes.","label":[[12,19,"NORP"],[61,68,"NORP"]]}
{"text":"Nightlife In Barcelona: Prepare To Stay Up Late (PHOTOS). Barcelona is a partygoer's paradise, with more travelers seeing the Spanish sunrise than the sunset, making it an absolute can't-miss destination for any visitor serious about their nightlife.","label":[[58,67,"ORG"],[126,133,"NORP"]]}
{"text":"Colorado Man Allegedly Shoots Son Dead After Mistaking Him For Intruder. Frank Leo Huner Jr. faces a second-degree murder charge.","label":[[0,8,"GPE"],[73,92,"PERSON"],[101,107,"ORDINAL"]]}
{"text":"Sasha Pieterse Almost Played Hanna On 'Pretty Little Liars'. This video shows how different PLL could have been.","label":[[0,34,"PERSON"],[92,95,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"The U.S. Is Part Of A War In Yemen, And Neither Clinton Nor Trump Will Talk About It. There's no evidence the next president has a plan forward for the country where American ally Saudi Arabia has been slaughtering civilians.","label":[[4,8,"GPE"],[29,34,"GPE"],[40,59,"PERSON"],[166,174,"NORP"],[180,192,"GPE"]]}
{"text":"'Real Housewives' Star's Husband Sentenced To 8 Years In Prison. ","label":[[25,32,"PERSON"],[46,53,"DATE"],[57,63,"GPE"]]}
{"text":"A U.S. Cyclist Made Sure She Won Gold, Then Collapsed To The Ground. Soon after, Kristin Armstrong's son rushed out to give her a hug.","label":[[2,6,"GPE"],[81,100,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"What Mount Greenwood's Reaction To Joshua Beal's Death Says About White Chicago. The tragic murder of another Black person by a police officer and the reactions of the community to the death show us once again that racism is alive and well.","label":[[5,22,"LOC"],[35,48,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"The 'Leisure Gap' Between Mothers And Fathers. In America, fathers, on average, have about three hours more leisure time per week than mothers. This “leisure gap” has been","label":[[5,17,"PERSON"],[50,57,"GPE"],[85,102,"TIME"]]}
{"text":"4 Ways Fathers Can Heal Themselves, Their Relationship With Their Children And The World. For all good fathers, science is on your side. Being present from day one is important. For example, in hormonal studies","label":[[0,1,"CARDINAL"]]}
{"text":"Leaked Emails Suggest DNC Was Conspiring Against Bernie Sanders. Looks like Sanders supporters weren't just being paranoid after all.","label":[[0,25,"ORG"],[76,83,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"Paris Train Hero Alek Skarlatos Reacts To Shooting At His Alma Mater. The National Guardsman, who attended Umpqua Community College, is \"heading home\" to Roseburg.","label":[[0,5,"GPE"],[58,68,"PERSON"],[70,92,"ORG"],[107,131,"ORG"],[154,162,"FAC"]]}
{"text":"La Mer Moisturizing Cream: From The Stylelist Network. From Color Makes All The Difference: Finally got my fave! Realized I couldn't live without it. Courtesy photo Read more on","label":[[0,25,"PERSON"],[32,53,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"Birthright Didn't Kill American IDF Soldier Max Steinberg. Max Steinberg, a Los Angeles native who upped and moved to Israel alone to volunteer with the Israeli Defense Forces died in combat on Sunday. But according to an editor at Slate, it wasn't Hamas who killed this 24-year-old.","label":[[23,31,"NORP"],[44,57,"PERSON"],[59,72,"PERSON"],[76,87,"GPE"],[118,124,"GPE"],[149,175,"ORG"],[194,200,"DATE"],[232,237,"ORG"],[249,254,"ORG"],[271,282,"DATE"]]}
{"text":"Daily Meditation: Love At Last. We all need help maintaining our personal spiritual practice. We hope that these Daily Meditations, prayers and mindful awareness","label":[[107,130,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"American Apparel Casting Call Says 'Instagram Hoes' Not Welcomed. ","label":[[0,36,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"Florida's Supreme Court Finally Takes a Stand for Victims of Medical Malpractice. As a Florida personal injury attorney who has worked hard to help injured patients and their families, I believe that this decision comes 11 years too late.","label":[[0,7,"GPE"],[10,23,"ORG"],[61,80,"ORG"],[87,94,"GPE"],[220,228,"DATE"]]}
{"text":"Divorced and Dateless? 5 Steps To Getting Back In The Dating Game. When you first got divorced, you proclaimed that you would never be in another relationship again. Now that you have spent enough time licking your wounds, you're contemplating the possibility of getting back in the game.","label":[[23,24,"CARDINAL"],[50,65,"WORK_OF_ART"],[76,81,"ORDINAL"]]}
{"text":"Guy's Attempt To Take Rattlesnake Selfie Ends With $153,000 Bill. Let thissss be a cautionary tale.","label":[[0,3,"PERSON"],[6,45,"WORK_OF_ART"],[52,59,"MONEY"]]}
{"text":"Mia Rose Storrie, Declared Dead Before Birth, Comes Home A 'Miracle'. After seven agonizing minutes, doctors found Mia Rose's faint heartbeat. An emergency team performed a desperate Caesarian","label":[[0,16,"PERSON"],[76,99,"TIME"],[115,125,"PERSON"],[183,192,"NORP"]]}
{"text":"Donald Trump Asks Congress To Pass $1 Trillion In Infrastructure Investment. “This effort will be guided by two core principles: Buy American, and hire American.\"","label":[[0,12,"PERSON"],[35,46,"MONEY"],[108,111,"CARDINAL"],[133,141,"NORP"],[152,160,"NORP"]]}
{"text":"Maui Football Coach Arrested For Allegedly Sexting Student. ","label":[[0,58,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"When Your Child Prefers One Parent Over Another. While this can be quite hurtful for the parent who is being excluded, it is helpful to know this, too, is a phase and will pass. Preferring one parent or adult to another, is actually considered healthy development and common among children of all ages.","label":[[189,192,"CARDINAL"]]}
{"text":"Rand Paul Wants GOP To Join Black Lives Matter Town Hall. \"If we were smart, we would do it.\"","label":[[0,15,"PERSON"],[16,19,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"Bill Maher Criticizes Mitt Romney's Charitable Donations To Mormon Church (VIDEO). Maher brushed off the Internet firestorm that came from the right after last week's episode, saying that he's \"really sorry","label":[[0,21,"PERSON"],[60,73,"ORG"],[155,166,"DATE"]]}
{"text":"Obama Administration Outlines Path For Climate Change Resiliency. In the last decade, extreme weather and wildfires cost the federal government $357 billion.","label":[[0,64,"ORG"],[69,84,"DATE"],[144,156,"MONEY"]]}
{"text":"Arresting Portraits Give Voices To Homeless People In America's Poorest Big City. ","label":[[54,61,"GPE"],[64,80,"LOC"]]}
{"text":"Rep. Darrell Issa Suggests Trump-Russia Inquiry Needs Special Prosecutor, Not Jeff Sessions. \"You cannot have somebody who was on the campaign and who is an appointee,\" the GOP congressman says.","label":[[5,39,"PERSON"],[173,176,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"Putting the Oxygen Back into Improving Education. In the time remaining for his administration, Secretary Duncan can still make his place in history by rebalancing the educational reform initiatives in favor of providing more constructive supports for teachers.","label":[[29,48,"ORG"],[106,112,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"Ceasefire Over? Jimmy Kimmel Shreds Sean Hannity And ‘Those Dummies On Fox & Friends’. The \"Jimmy Kimmel Live\" host says they'd believe in lizard people... if Trump said it first.","label":[[16,28,"PERSON"],[36,48,"PERSON"],[71,85,"ORG"],[92,109,"WORK_OF_ART"],[159,164,"ORG"],[173,178,"ORDINAL"]]}
{"text":"Like Food Trucks For Shopping: 11 Mobile Stores To Visit (PHOTOS). The phrase \"truck shop\" does not conjure images of sartorial grandeur. But call it the next iteration of the food cart phenomenon, and we bet you're intrigued.","label":[[31,33,"CARDINAL"]]}
{"text":"Lena Dunham And Jack Antonoff Split After 5 Years Together. A source tells E! News the pair split up in December.","label":[[0,11,"PERSON"],[16,35,"PERSON"],[104,112,"DATE"]]}
{"text":"Obesity as Disease: Why I Vote No. There is a certain irony in the nearly immediate juxtaposition of the rare introduction of a new FDA-approved drug for weight loss (Belviq) to the marketplace and the recognition of obesity as a \"disease\" by the AMA. A line from the movie Jerry Maguire comes to mind: \"You complete me!\"","label":[[132,135,"ORG"],[247,250,"ORG"],[274,287,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"Brooklynites, Bike Accidents and the Science of Compassion. What's critical to compassion is that it unites this understanding of others' distress with the motivation to alleviate that distress. Helping behavior further requires the cognitive and behavioral resources to act on that motivation.","label":[[14,28,"PERSON"],[33,58,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"An Incredible Road Trip Through West Texas. Texas native Stephen Orr takes the road less traveled on a drive through the Lone Star State's wild western borderlands.","label":[[37,42,"GPE"],[44,49,"GPE"],[57,68,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"Court Throws Out Some Of Former Illinois Gov. Rod Blagojevich's Criminal Charges. Blagojevich was convicted for trying to make money out of his power to appoint a replacement for Barack Obama, who was leaving his seat in the U.S. Senate representing Illinois after winning the presidential election in 2008.","label":[[32,40,"GPE"],[46,63,"PERSON"],[179,191,"PERSON"],[225,236,"ORG"],[250,258,"GPE"],[302,306,"DATE"]]}
{"text":"Kim Davis Wants The Law To Forget That Time She Defied The Supreme Court On Gay Marriage. And she just may get her wish.","label":[[0,15,"PERSON"],[55,72,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"Go the Distance! Hiking With Your Dog. Learn about your dog's limits physically, take the heat into consideration, and have a time limit for your hike. If their tongue is hanging out of their mouth more than half way, it's a sign to stop and take a rest.","label":[[198,212,"CARDINAL"]]}
{"text":"How Nonprofits Make Our Lives Livable. Following disasters like Hurricanes Harvey and Irma, where would we be without the emergency relief and long-term rebuilding work provided by nonprofits?","label":[[64,81,"PERSON"],[86,90,"GPE"]]}
{"text":"A Coral Detail: From The Stylelist Network. From Kailani's Korner: Coral is my ultimate favorite color. Every time I catch a glimpse of this color, it generates such","label":[[21,42,"ORG"],[49,56,"PERSON"],[59,65,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"Can Social Networks Cure Disease? Part II. Acute disease can be left to the hospitals, but creating health and healing of chronic disease seems to happen best in the community -- with people helping people where each one of us lives, where we eat, cook, learn, work, play and pray.","label":[[0,32,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"I Didn't Lose My Self To Motherhood, And Neither Should You.. Being a mother isn't a distraction from who we are.","label":[[9,35,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"13 Hair Mistakes You Need To Stop Making. 13. Skipping nightly hair maintenance: A lot of women don't do anything to their hair at night. So Kimble recommends investing","label":[[0,2,"CARDINAL"],[42,44,"CARDINAL"],[55,62,"DATE"],[131,136,"TIME"]]}
{"text":"9 Things You're Doing To Ruin Your Hardwood Floors Without Even Realizing It. Trying To Keep Your Throw Rugs In Place A throw rug can go from pretty to pesky in 2.5 seconds, or the minute they start","label":[[0,1,"CARDINAL"],[16,76,"WORK_OF_ART"],[161,172,"TIME"],[177,187,"TIME"]]}
{"text":"LISTEN: The Woman Who 'Sees' Like A Bat. ","label":[[0,6,"ORG"],[34,39,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"Lessons Learned Training for First Marathon. The 26.2 miles I will run on November 4 may be for my father and other stroke survivors, but this race has become about so much more.  Since deciding to run the marathon, I have traveled over 900 miles by foot, and spent nearly 140 hours training.","label":[[49,59,"QUANTITY"],[74,84,"DATE"],[232,246,"QUANTITY"],[266,282,"TIME"]]}
{"text":"4 Steps to Detoxify Your Kitchen. Most likely, the food industry holds your kitchen hostage. No doubt your cupboards and pantry are filled with ultra-processed fare. Detoxifying your kitchen allows you to escape these shackles and transform your kitchen to a place of wellness.","label":[[0,1,"CARDINAL"]]}
{"text":"As Many States Roll Back Abortion Access, New York's Governor Wants To Protect It. He proposed changing the state's constitution to protect Roe v. Wade.","label":[[42,52,"GPE"],[140,151,"LAW"]]}
{"text":"'SNL' Mocks Fiscal Cliff Talks In Cold Open (VIDEO). Saturday Night Live took on the fiscal cliff negotiations this week. House Speaker John Boehner and President Barack Obama","label":[[1,4,"ORG"],[6,30,"ORG"],[53,72,"WORK_OF_ART"],[111,120,"DATE"],[122,127,"ORG"],[136,148,"PERSON"],[163,175,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"Job Listing: Member Of Congress (No Experience Required). House rules apply.","label":[[23,31,"ORG"],[58,63,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"The Accidental Sensuality Of Ancient Indian Wrestling. ","label":[[0,53,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"Hong Kong Actor Wears 'Brown Face,' Highlights Prejudice Among Asians. This type of stereotyping might be due to a lack of a “pan-Asian” identity.","label":[[0,15,"GPE"],[126,135,"NORP"]]}
{"text":"LOOK: One Of Heaviest MLB Players Ever Looks Like A New Man. ","label":[[6,9,"CARDINAL"]]}
{"text":"Soul-Talk: Can Forgiveness Be Its Own Form of Poison?. But how do you move from resentment, upset and blame into acceptance, understanding and true forgiveness? The answer lies in forgiving yourself.  Not forgiving yourself for an action, thought, word or deed aimed at another, but forgiving yourself for having judged yourself in the first place.","label":[[0,9,"PERSON"],[336,341,"ORDINAL"]]}
{"text":"Taylor Swift Is Done Talking About Her Twitter Feud With Nicki Minaj. She's over it.","label":[[0,28,"PERSON"],[57,68,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"What Does A Sleep-Deprived Trump Dream About?. Besides China.","label":[[10,38,"WORK_OF_ART"],[55,60,"GPE"]]}
{"text":"Casey Neistat Records Journey To New York For Foursquare Co-Founder's Wedding. See Casey skate through Paris traffic to catch the first flight out Saturday morning, to land in NYC at 1:30 PM. Besides","label":[[0,29,"PERSON"],[33,77,"ORG"],[83,88,"PERSON"],[103,108,"GPE"],[147,155,"DATE"],[156,163,"TIME"],[176,179,"FAC"],[183,190,"TIME"]]}
{"text":"'Black Panther' Cast Made Sandra Bullock Cry 'As A Mother'. “I’m so grateful to Marvel because about five years ago, my son asked me if there were any brown Legos... and I don’t have to turn them brown anymore.”","label":[[1,15,"PERSON"],[80,86,"GPE"],[95,115,"DATE"]]}
{"text":"Best Airlines: Airline Quality Rating Ranks American Carriers (PHOTOS). According to the survey, the performance of leading U.S. carriers has improved for the fourth consecutive year, earning the","label":[[0,13,"ORG"],[124,128,"GPE"],[155,182,"DATE"]]}
{"text":"What It's Like Being A Kid Who Has The 'Opposite Of Autism'. A new book explores a young boy's life with the rare Williams syndrome.","label":[[114,122,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"How Wall Street Could Profit From Cheating (on Spouses). The wizards of Wall Street never leave your side. They’re on hand to make money off you at every stage of life — in sickness","label":[[47,54,"GPE"]]}
{"text":"Southwest Airlines Flight Diverted Over 'Suspicious Behavior'. Several passengers were \"unruly,\" an FBI spokesperson said.","label":[[0,41,"ORG"],[100,103,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"Stranger On Bus Shuts Down Bigot After His Ignorant Comment To Muslim Mom. \"It shows people are willing to stand up to ignorance and hate on behalf of others.\"","label":[[63,69,"NORP"]]}
{"text":"Martin Brodeur Falls: Devils Goalie Gets Lucky Against Penguins (VIDEO). The 40-year-old goalie, completely off-balanced, tried to keep himself from accidentally tapping the puck into his own net","label":[[0,20,"PERSON"],[77,88,"DATE"]]}
{"text":"Here's How Mast Brothers Chocolate Stands Up Against The Big Ones. We put it up against Hershey's and Godiva to see if we could taste a difference.","label":[[88,95,"ORG"],[102,108,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"John Dickerson Will Take Over 'Face The Nation'. ","label":[[0,24,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"Airplane Proposal: Flight Instructor Pops The Question Up In The Air (VIDEO). Long Islander Mike Nelson has got to be one of the most romantic flight instructors in New York. The proposal wasn't a complete","label":[[0,17,"PERSON"],[92,103,"PERSON"],[165,173,"GPE"]]}
{"text":"Weekly Roundup of eBay Vintage Clothing Finds. This eclectic mix of designer and non-designer vintage clothing and accessories caught my discerning eye because of its uniqueness","label":[[18,22,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"4 Ways to Make Cooking at Home Doable -- and More Fun. Maybe you'll never can bushels of green beans, make your own ketchup, or grind your own hamburger. And that's fine. Cooking in your kitchen doesn't ever need to be an obsessive big deal. All it needs to be is a chance for you to enjoy yourself, learn something new, and feel good about what you've done.","label":[[2,22,"EVENT"],[26,37,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"Kim Gordon And Arcade Fire Are In A Short Film Together, Commence Collective Squee. ","label":[[0,10,"PERSON"],[34,82,"WORK_OF_ART"]]}
{"text":"Irish Prime Minister Uses St. Patrick's Day To Praise Immigration In Front Of Trump. \"We came ― and we became ― Americans.”","label":[[0,5,"NORP"],[21,39,"PERSON"],[110,121,"NORP"]]}
{"text":"Alex Trebek's Former Home On Mulholland Drive Is For Sale For $3.9 Million (PHOTOS). Those \"Beetlejuice\" inspired chairs don't look like they could have been purchased during this decade. But, with the right","label":[[0,13,"PERSON"],[62,74,"MONEY"],[175,186,"DATE"]]}
{"text":"'You're Making Mama Sad' Is a Dirty, Dirty Lie. If I try to stop the tantrums by telling my daughter that she's making me unhappy, the not-so-subtle message is that I am not in control of my own happiness. And nothing could be more dangerous.","label":[[30,35,"ORG"],[37,46,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"Financial Independence for Everyone: 6 Steps to Leaving Work Behind. Reaching financial independence requires some effort, sacrifice, and learning on your part. Many people shy away from planning their finances because they lack an understanding of economics and financial markets. I've found that managing finances wisely depends on some basic principles that anyone can understand.","label":[[37,38,"CARDINAL"]]}
{"text":"IEX Wins SEC Approval As U.S. Stock Exchange. A built-in delay would protect investors from traders who use tactics depicted in Michael Lewis' 2014 book \"Flash Boys: A Wall Street Revolt.\"","label":[[9,12,"ORG"],[25,44,"ORG"],[128,142,"PERSON"],[143,147,"DATE"],[154,164,"WORK_OF_ART"]]}
{"text":"5 Things You Are Doing That Keep You From Feeling You Are Good Enough. One of the foundational principles I use while helping my clients is identifying and owning their feelings of worthiness and being good enough about who they are and what they stand for. It is from this place of self-worth that your internal genius shows up so you can truly offer your gifts to the world.","label":[[71,74,"CARDINAL"]]}
{"text":"C.Z. Guest Wears White On White... And How To Get The Look (PHOTO). Time & Life Pictures\/Getty Images BCBG Jacquard Dress, Nine West Ballet Flats, Zara Blazer, Dana Buchman Pearl & Crystal","label":[[68,121,"ORG"],[123,145,"ORG"],[147,158,"PERSON"],[160,178,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"New-Age Guilt. When we go for the blame, we end up as victims for ourselves or others. When we take responsibility, the whole discussion on blame, guilt and shame becomes completely unnecessary. All we have to do is to take our part of the responsibility and readjust the course.","label":[[0,13,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"Chris Murphy Wants A New Progressive Foreign Policy. The Connecticut senator's vision stands out among Democrats.","label":[[0,12,"PERSON"],[57,68,"GPE"],[103,112,"NORP"]]}
{"text":"Trump Surrogate Really Just Goes For It With Full-On Jay Z Attack. To which we ask: Is this a good strategy?","label":[[53,65,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"Smoothing The Frictions Between Parent And Nanny. It wasn’t that Kimberly Van Der Beek’s new nanny was unqualified. She had come with sparkling references and a gold-star","label":[[65,88,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"The Parking Lot of Love. I do believe there's someone for everyone, but the more I thought about it, the more I realized while love is not transactional, it sometimes can turn ugly and into hatred when you do not create the boundaries necessary for you to love yourself.","label":[[0,23,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"Pet Shop Boys: Finding Your Furry Partner. You don't have to have kids to get a pet. Some couples have been known to adopt a dog or cat as a practice family. Would Biff and Brenda make responsible parents? If they strap Ruffy to the roof of their Range Rover, probably not.","label":[[28,41,"PERSON"],[164,168,"PERSON"],[173,179,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"In This Fragile Sacred Space. These days, their adventures rarely include me, and my job as mom isn't to hold their hands. My job now is to feel their acceleration, their hunger for flight... and let go.","label":[[3,28,"ORG"],[30,40,"DATE"]]}
{"text":"No One Knew How To Take Seth Meyers' Harvey Weinstein Joke. The Golden Globes host took on sexual harassment and Donald Trump in a tricky monologue.","label":[[37,58,"PERSON"],[60,77,"PERSON"],[113,125,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"Jeb Bush Will Appear On Stephen Colbert's First 'Late Show'. He'll join George Clooney and Kendrick Lamar.","label":[[0,20,"PERSON"],[24,41,"PERSON"],[42,47,"ORDINAL"],[49,59,"WORK_OF_ART"],[72,86,"PERSON"],[91,105,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"The Village Voice: Hail And Farewell, Friend. I hate to think the internet killed the print edition of the Village Voice this week, but that is the truth. Just as the","label":[[0,44,"ORG"],[103,120,"ORG"],[121,130,"DATE"]]}
{"text":"Do All Men Getting Testosterone Therapy Actually Need It?. \"Over the past decade, older and middle-aged men are increasingly being tested for low testosterone levels and being prescribed","label":[[65,80,"DATE"]]}
{"text":"How ISIS Is Redrawing Iraq's Map. ","label":[[22,26,"GPE"],[29,32,"GPE"]]}
{"text":"The History Of The Irish Car Bomb, And Why You Probably Shouldn't Ever Order One. You might want to think twice before you order one.","label":[[0,33,"WORK_OF_ART"]]}
{"text":"Off-The-Wall Ice Cream Flavors. Some people may think September is the end of ice cream season. We just think it means it's time to get more creative.","label":[[54,63,"DATE"]]}
{"text":"U.S.-Cuba Relations: Why It Matters To All Of Us. Cuba is now the gateway for America’s foreign policy in Latin America.","label":[[46,48,"GPE"],[50,54,"GPE"],[78,85,"GPE"],[106,119,"LOC"]]}
{"text":"Calle 13's Rene Perez Receives Nobel Peace Summit Award. Rene Perez has been awarded a Nobel Peace Summit Award for his song lyrics and his support for social causes. The rapper","label":[[6,8,"CARDINAL"],[11,30,"PERSON"],[31,55,"WORK_OF_ART"],[57,67,"PERSON"],[85,111,"WORK_OF_ART"]]}
{"text":"Refrigerator Magnet Designs: How To Pimp Your Fridge (PHOTOS). Sure, you know that you can trick out your stand mixer, but did you know that you can also pimp your fridge? Yep, you read","label":[[172,175,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"Armani Fall 2012 Show Features Hats... And Flats! (VIDEO). \"Once a symbol of power, today the woman’s jacket has become practical attire, with pockets to hold mobiles and accessories","label":[[84,89,"DATE"]]}
{"text":"Reverse Crowdfund-gineering: Five Ways to Integrate Events into your Crowdfunding Campaign. Review some of the events that successful campaigns organized or participated in, and model their success. This is another way you can make reverse crowdfund-gineering work for you.","label":[[29,33,"CARDINAL"],[34,58,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"New Cecil The Lion Beanie Baby Sales To Be Donated To Wildlife Conservation. The company hopes the plush toy will provide comfort to those saddened by Cecil's death.","label":[[0,9,"ORG"],[151,156,"LOC"]]}
{"text":"Michael Symon's Love Letter To Cleveland. Cleveland native and Chef Michael Symon grew up in a Greek and Sicilian family. The 2008 winner of The Next Iron Chef, Symon","label":[[0,15,"PERSON"],[16,27,"WORK_OF_ART"],[31,40,"GPE"],[42,51,"GPE"],[68,81,"PERSON"],[95,100,"NORP"],[105,113,"NORP"],[126,130,"DATE"],[141,159,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"Christian Fashion Line Is Brainchild Of Former Model, Kylie Bisutti (PHOTOS). Doesn't ring a bell? Well, Kylie is here to remind you with her all-new Christian clothing line, God Inspired, or Gi. The","label":[[0,67,"ORG"],[150,159,"NORP"],[175,187,"PERSON"],[192,194,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"Eulogy for a Herding Dog. Like any good dog, Mike enriched our family. And even in death, he's helping us teach a heartbreaking, yet vital lesson to our boys.","label":[[45,49,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"Theo And Beau (And Their Mom) Get A Book Deal. Jean Feiwel, senior vice president and director of the Macmillan Children's Publishing Group (of which Feiwel & Friends is","label":[[9,13,"PERSON"],[34,45,"WORK_OF_ART"],[47,58,"PERSON"],[98,139,"ORG"],[150,166,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"Joe Biden Slams Donald Trump For Selling 'Sick Message' On Immigration. \"There's one guy absolutely denigrating an entire group of people, appealing to the baser side of human nature, working on this notion of xenophobia in a way that hasn't occurred in a long time.\"","label":[[0,28,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"Trump And Netanyahu: Embracing Illusions, Ignoring Reality. Netanyahu has found in Trump a co-conspirator.","label":[[10,19,"PERSON"],[60,69,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"Christie On Clinton Speech: 'I Thought That Elizabeth Warren Wasn't Running'. ","label":[[0,8,"ORG"],[12,26,"PERSON"],[44,60,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"Watch Out For Sleepy Drivers This Thanksgiving. Thanksgiving is a time of travel, but one expert warns that sleep deprivation and darkness can cause drivers to become sleepy","label":[[29,46,"DATE"],[48,60,"DATE"],[86,89,"CARDINAL"]]}
{"text":"Trump University Lawsuit Survives Dismissal Attempt. Plaintiffs claim they were defrauded by Trump's real estate seminars.","label":[[0,51,"ORG"],[93,98,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"Munich Travel: Opera With A Beer Chaser. As the Michelin guide says of three-star restaurants, Munich's opera and food were both \"Worth the journey.\"","label":[[0,13,"ORG"],[28,39,"PERSON"],[48,56,"PERSON"],[71,76,"CARDINAL"],[95,101,"GPE"]]}
{"text":"The Making Of 'No Reservations' (VIDEO). A new web-video series shows the behind-the-scenes making of Anthony Bourdain's \"No Reservations,\" giving a unique look at","label":[[0,31,"WORK_OF_ART"],[102,120,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"How Cake Became The Favorite Mode For Debate Over LGBT Rights, Other Issues. NEW YORK (AP) — It should be a piece of cake. Customer comes in, asks for a cake with a specific design or for a particular","label":[[77,85,"GPE"],[87,89,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"Watch That Stunning 'Creation' Scene From 'Noah'. ","label":[[43,47,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"Trump Threatens To Cut Aid To UN Members Over Jerusalem Vote. \"Well, we’re watching those votes,\" the president said.","label":[[0,32,"ORG"],[46,60,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"Charlottesville Shows That States Must Amend Their Open-Carry Laws. A Virginia statute passed in 1997 precludes Charlottesville from exercising any common sense in such situations.","label":[[70,78,"GPE"],[97,101,"DATE"]]}
{"text":"Sleep Better To Get Your Energy Back. By Mary Kate Frank \"The main reason I see for loss of energy in women is that they have too much to do,\" says Michael Roizen","label":[[41,56,"PERSON"],[148,162,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"Everything's Coming Up Crazy On The Midseason Return Of 'How To Get Away With Murder'. Welcome back.","label":[[0,85,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"Cadbury Eggs vs. Peeps: Which Is Better? (POLL). This is not so much a question of which came first, but more so of which is better -- the chick(en) or the egg? We're not","label":[[0,12,"ORG"],[94,99,"ORDINAL"]]}
{"text":"Donald Trump Floats Gross New Conspiracy Theory About Barack Obama. \"You just look at the body language and there’s something going on,\" the presumptive GOP nominee said.","label":[[0,40,"PERSON"],[54,66,"PERSON"],[153,156,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"Top 5 Tastes: 'Tis the Beginning of the Chowdown Season. Turkey quickly segues into decoratively iced cookies, eggnog and ham, and before we know it, January 2nd rolls around, and the champagne toasts turn to champagne bloats. But let's rejoice! It's just the beginning, and stuffing, lobster bisque and some eggplant pizza are getting me on track!","label":[[57,63,"GPE"],[150,161,"DATE"]]}
{"text":"Couple Stole $35,000 From Missing Plane Victims, Police Say. ","label":[[14,20,"MONEY"],[26,47,"ORG"],[49,59,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"It's Time For The Eagles To Cut Ties With Chip Kelly. Philadelphia, at 1-3, ranks 30th in offense and 30th on third down.","label":[[54,66,"GPE"],[71,74,"CARDINAL"],[82,86,"ORDINAL"],[102,106,"ORDINAL"],[110,115,"ORDINAL"]]}
{"text":"Bush's Ethics Lawyer: Jeff Sessions May Go To Jail If He Lied To Congress. The Attorney General is accused of lying to Congress about conversations with the Russia ambassador.","label":[[0,4,"PERSON"],[7,20,"PERSON"],[22,35,"PERSON"],[65,73,"ORG"],[119,127,"ORG"],[157,163,"GPE"]]}
{"text":"Trump Returns To White House Without Melania As CBS Airs Stormy Daniels Interview. The first lady is spending spring break in Florida.","label":[[0,13,"PERSON"],[37,45,"GPE"],[48,81,"ORG"],[87,92,"ORDINAL"],[126,133,"GPE"]]}
{"text":"Retroactive Update: August 5-12. It has been such a great privilege these last two weeks to visit old friends and make new ones. One question that inevitably continues to come up as I visit more people is what I will do after the run.","label":[[0,18,"ORG"],[20,31,"DATE"],[68,88,"DATE"],[129,132,"CARDINAL"]]}
{"text":"Lindsey Graham's Leaked Voicemails Are Very Revealing. As usual, Donald Trump comes off as a logical and reasonable human being.","label":[[0,16,"PERSON"],[65,77,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"Roy Moore, Bill Clinton, Donald Trump And Sexual 'Whataboutism'. Moore’s “What about Clinton” defense is no defense at all, but it is food for serious thought.","label":[[0,9,"PERSON"],[11,23,"PERSON"],[25,37,"PERSON"],[85,92,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"Obama Profiles Parkland Survivors For TIME's '100 Most Influential' List. The high school students \"are shaking us out of our complacency.”","label":[[0,44,"ORG"],[46,49,"CARDINAL"]]}
{"text":"Elizabeth Warren Asks Obama To Replace Wall Street Regulator For 'Brazen Conduct'. The progressive firebrand has long warred with SEC Chair Mary Jo White, a former corporate lawyer.","label":[[0,16,"PERSON"],[130,139,"ORG"],[140,153,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"Two Iowa Energy Headlines That Say a Lot About the Electricity Market and Policy Changes. \"We opted for what was in the best interest of our customers,\" MidAmerican vice president for regulatory affairs Dean Crist","label":[[0,3,"CARDINAL"],[153,164,"ORG"],[203,213,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"Justin Trudeau Praises Women's March As Inspirational. The Canadian prime minister offered a bilingual message of support.","label":[[0,14,"PERSON"],[31,36,"DATE"],[59,67,"NORP"]]}
{"text":"Why Am I Marching? It's Personal. I'm a New Yorker. Living in NY is what I can speak from the heart about. We're a tough bunch and along with the rest of the world, we're taking a beating from climate change. Here's why I am marching to protect what I love, my New York.","label":[[38,50,"ORG"],[62,64,"GPE"],[261,269,"GPE"]]}
{"text":"The Best Way To Use Leftover Rice. Just call it “sun rice.” Rice and its summer versions are one of Italy’s most popular dishes in the hottest months of the","label":[[0,33,"PERSON"],[60,64,"PERSON"],[73,79,"DATE"],[93,96,"CARDINAL"],[100,105,"GPE"],[131,149,"DATE"]]}
{"text":"United States Only First-World Country Without Mandatory Paid Maternity Leave: 'A Human Rights Issue' (VIDEO). \"Women are being booby trapped left and right,\" Rigg added. \"We're throwing moms and babies under the bus. This is very serious","label":[[0,13,"GPE"],[159,163,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"Wings of Kilimanjaro: Is It Possible?. What could you do that pushes you to the limit physically, mentally and emotionally and leaves the planet stronger than it was when you stepped through your front door and set out on your life-changing adventure?","label":[[0,20,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"40 Years Ago To The Day, 'Doctor Who' Predicted 'Alternative Facts'. The powerful \"alter the facts to fit the views,\" the Doctor said on Jan. 22, 1977.","label":[[0,23,"DATE"],[137,150,"DATE"]]}
{"text":"Comedian Jerry Lewis Dead At 91. The beloved comic enjoyed a decades-long career.","label":[[0,8,"NORP"],[9,25,"PERSON"],[29,31,"DATE"],[61,68,"DATE"]]}
{"text":"Today's 'Voter Fraud' Efforts Recall Infamous 1990 Attempt To Deter Black Vote. The late Sen. Jesse Helms would likely approve.","label":[[0,5,"DATE"],[94,105,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"A Watergate Prosecutor And Nixon Scholar Grade Trump After One Month. Sadly, a little more than a month after his inauguration, he seems to be well beyond the Nixon paranoia.","label":[[0,22,"EVENT"],[27,32,"PERSON"],[59,68,"DATE"],[86,103,"DATE"],[159,164,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"Why A Backlash Against Refugees Only Helps ISIS. “The more that happens, the more French Muslims feel alienated and are susceptible to extremist recruitment,\" one analyst says.","label":[[82,96,"NORP"],[159,162,"CARDINAL"]]}
{"text":"Bernie Sanders Says It's Time To 'Rethink' The Electoral College. The Vermont senator wants to have \"serious discussion\" about a system that can send the loser of the popular vote to the White House.","label":[[0,14,"PERSON"],[43,64,"ORG"],[70,77,"GPE"],[183,198,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"Trump Supporters Are Not Oppressed. New York Times readers were confronted today with a new entry in the paper’s ongoing competition for the most ill-conceived","label":[[0,34,"PERSON"],[36,50,"ORG"],[75,80,"DATE"]]}
{"text":"Senior Volunteer Honorees Make Communities Better. Ira and Barbara Smith of Acton, Mass., have been making dreams come true since 1990. When they heard about an El Salvadoran","label":[[7,49,"PERSON"],[51,54,"PERSON"],[59,72,"PERSON"],[76,81,"GPE"],[83,88,"GPE"],[130,134,"DATE"]]}
{"text":"Questioning Authority in the School of Athens. On a recent trip to Rome, I was walking through the halls of the Vatican museums and after entering one of the Raphael rooms, I turned my head to discover, to my amazement, my favorite fresco: The School of Athens.","label":[[0,21,"ORG"],[25,45,"ORG"],[67,71,"GPE"],[112,119,"FAC"],[147,150,"CARDINAL"],[158,165,"PERSON"],[240,260,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"This Muffuletta Dip Is The One Recipe You Need To Make This Weekend. Perfect eats for Sunday football.","label":[[86,92,"DATE"]]}
{"text":"Armed Suspects Used Periscope To Hunt For Man: Sacramento Police. Viewers watching on Periscope egged on the suspects and encouraged them to use the gun.","label":[[0,29,"ORG"],[86,95,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"Wendy Davis: 'I F**king Hate To Lose'. Still, she said that she hasn't been discouraged from taking on uphill battles.","label":[[0,11,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"Kansas Official Shows Slides Of Criminals Named Mohammed. He said he was providing \"a public warning for citizens.\"","label":[[0,6,"GPE"]]}
{"text":"Time-Lapse Videos Of A Hyperrealist Master Will Make You Lose Your Damn Mind. Emmy Kalia has skills. And she wants to walk you through each and every one of them.","label":[[0,10,"ORG"],[78,88,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"How a Sanitary Pad Project in India Benefits Both Girls' Education and the Environment. ","label":[[30,35,"GPE"]]}
{"text":"Childhood Revised. Fiction of all sorts, including nursery rhymes, allows us to try out conflict in a safe way. That's the point, it's where the thrill comes in; we're scared, then reassured the danger isn't real.","label":[[0,17,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"Can One Christmas Gift Change a Life?. ","label":[[4,7,"CARDINAL"]]}
{"text":"Federal Judge Temporarily Blocks Texas Law Banning D&E Abortions. The ruling comes after abortion providers sued the Texas Attorney General.","label":[[14,32,"PERSON"],[33,38,"GPE"],[117,122,"GPE"]]}
{"text":"Cannes 2013: Savoring the Opening Night Dinner by Chef Anne-Sophie Pic. Cannes is as much about food and gifts as it is about films.","label":[[22,46,"EVENT"],[50,70,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"Organize Your Cleaning Supplies. \"During your precious Saturday hours, an organized, fully stocked broom closet will save you time, motivate you, and remind","label":[[55,63,"DATE"],[64,69,"TIME"]]}
{"text":"Matthew McConaughey Defends Justin Bieber's Distaste For Shirts (VIDEO). Do you think Bieber's style is defendable? \"Really? Well, he keeps doing it in airports, right?\" Matthew responds. Get More","label":[[0,43,"PERSON"],[44,63,"FAC"],[86,92,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"Trump Calls Jeff Sessions 'Mr. Magoo' And Twitter Can't Get Over It. Trump's reported new nickname for his attorney general has people divided.","label":[[12,27,"PERSON"],[31,36,"PERSON"],[42,67,"WORK_OF_ART"],[69,74,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"'Thrive' in Action: Encouraging the Third Metric in Local Communities. As more and more conversation emerges about how we can best support individuals to thrive, I'd encourage others to consider creating similar types of supportive gatherings in their communities. Along with whatever structures can be added to our workplaces and our daily routines, sometimes we also need to create a village of support in order to sustain the values we most believe in.","label":[[335,340,"DATE"]]}
{"text":"Instagram Account Documents The Varied And Vibrant Dancers Of NYC. James Jin wants to photograph dancers in every New York City subway station there is.","label":[[67,76,"PERSON"],[114,127,"GPE"]]}
{"text":"Thiel Shows Why Tech Billionaires Are The New Robber Barons. Destroying Gawker is not just revenge or a kind of political act, it’s in Thiel’s words “philanthropic.”","label":[[61,78,"PERSON"],[135,140,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"Stitch and Hitch. Doing it DIY is a perfect way to add some fun to the oft-mocked tradition of the wedding shower.","label":[[27,30,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"Cancer Messed With the Wrong B*tch: Brownies or Bust. If you're not a doctor, please don't offer me medical advice. If you don't have cancer, don't tell me how I should be living my life. And actually, as a general rule, if you're not ME, don't tell me how I should be living MY life.","label":[[0,13,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"It's Reportedly Over For 'Bachelor' Stars Juan Pablo And Nikki. ","label":[[36,52,"PERSON"],[57,62,"GPE"]]}
{"text":"Ready, Set, Step. For me, it was that step, that first step, that was so difficult to take. As the new year approaches, we each have that once-yearly opportunity to create and recreate our own, personalized thousand-mile journey.  What's yours?","label":[[0,16,"ORG"],[49,54,"ORDINAL"],[95,107,"DATE"],[207,220,"QUANTITY"]]}
{"text":"Dear Jane Doe. When I wrote \"What All Mothers Must Do For Their Sons,\" it was not the first story that I intended to write for you. It was the second. The first? It was Dear Jane Doe, me too.","label":[[29,68,"WORK_OF_ART"],[86,91,"ORDINAL"],[143,149,"ORDINAL"],[155,160,"ORDINAL"]]}
{"text":"The Book of Negroes: Life, Liberty and Love. Based on the award-winning novel Someone Knows My Name by Lawrence Hill, The Book of Negroes tells the story of Aminata Diallo, an 11-year-old girl kidnapped from West Africa and her personal and spiritual journey as part of the Trans-Atlantic slave trade.","label":[[0,43,"WORK_OF_ART"],[78,99,"PERSON"],[103,116,"PERSON"],[118,137,"WORK_OF_ART"],[157,171,"ORG"],[176,187,"DATE"],[208,219,"GPE"],[270,288,"LAW"]]}
{"text":"Taraji, Kerry And Mary J. Redefine Squad Goals In New Apple Commercial. Unprecedented amounts of Black Girl Magic in only 62 seconds.","label":[[18,46,"PERSON"],[97,113,"PRODUCT"],[117,132,"TIME"]]}
{"text":"Life Imitates Art: When Cuban Actors Defect. Did the actors follow the script too closely? Actors Anailin de la Rua de la Torre and Javier Nunez Florian disappeared after their plane landed in Miami last week. They appear to have defected. Was life imitating art?","label":[[24,43,"ORG"],[112,127,"PERSON"],[132,152,"PERSON"],[193,198,"GPE"],[199,208,"DATE"]]}
{"text":"Atlanta Motel Standoff Ends With Suspect Stabbing Himself. DECATUR, Ga. (AP) — A standoff at a motel outside Atlanta that involved a number of children ended Tuesday morning with the","label":[[0,57,"ORG"],[68,71,"GPE"],[73,75,"ORG"],[109,116,"GPE"],[158,165,"DATE"],[166,173,"TIME"]]}
{"text":"Eleanore Regan, Woman With Brain Tumor, Gave Birth Last Week, Carried Olympic Torch. \"I feel proud to be able to carry the flame amongst such inspirational people and in such a beautiful city,\" Regan told the","label":[[0,14,"PERSON"],[27,38,"PERSON"],[40,50,"PERSON"],[51,60,"DATE"],[62,83,"ORG"],[194,199,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"Five Bars For A Study Abroad Budget (PHOTOS). While studying abroad may feel like an extended vacation most of the time, one thing is most certainly not luxurious about the experience: your ever-tightening budget.","label":[[0,4,"CARDINAL"],[121,124,"CARDINAL"]]}
{"text":"Nick Offerman Is Back With Another Marvelous Episode Of 'Shower Thoughts'. \"Every candy bar is fun-sized if you love candy. Or are on ecstasy.\"","label":[[0,13,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"Learning To Say \"No\" And \"Yes\" To Heal Our Lives. I used to not know how to say “no” to the people in my life–my clients, my family and friends. I didn’t want to disappoint","label":[[31,48,"WORK_OF_ART"]]}
{"text":"Woman Charged With Attempted Murder In Failed Coat Hanger Abortion. MURFREESBORO, Tenn. (AP) — A Tennessee woman is charged with attempted first-degree murder for what investigators say was","label":[[82,87,"GPE"],[89,91,"ORG"],[97,106,"GPE"],[139,144,"ORDINAL"]]}
{"text":"Refuse To Be Silenced By Trump Budget Insults. I am part of the 87 percent of the working class that has benefited from basic safety net policies.","label":[[60,74,"PERCENT"]]}
{"text":"College Presidents In Cleveland Would Rather Not Talk About Donald Trump. Most have nothing to say about the man being nominated for president in their city.","label":[[22,31,"GPE"],[60,72,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"Service Interrupted. They sit in my chair and breathe a sigh of relief for the opportunity to take one hour out of their hectic day for dedicated relaxation and pampering. But all of a sudden, when that little screen lights up or a handbag rumbles with an iPhone begging to be answered.","label":[[99,107,"TIME"],[115,131,"DATE"]]}
{"text":"'Green News Report' -- June 2, 2015. ","label":[[1,19,"ORG"],[23,35,"DATE"]]}
{"text":"Dad's Comics Nail The Hilarity Of Raising Kids Today. Chris Grady hopes his new book of comics resonates with other parents.","label":[[47,52,"DATE"],[54,65,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"Helicopter Proposal: Man Proposes To Girlfriend In Flight Over Beach (VIDEO). Click through the slideshows below to see some other in-flight proposals. Jonathan Salama spelled it all out for his girlfriend","label":[[0,19,"PERSON"],[152,167,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"Jennifer Aniston's Christmas Outfits Are Beach-Appropriate (PHOTOS). All she wants for Christmas are tan lines.","label":[[0,18,"PERSON"],[19,36,"EVENT"],[87,96,"DATE"]]}
{"text":"Russian Astronauts Encounter Glitch With Earth-Watching Cameras Installed During Spacewalk. The spacewalkers also planned to jettison the frame of an old material exposure experiment, as well as retrieve a case of","label":[[0,7,"NORP"]]}
{"text":"Dartmouth Posts Fundraising Record Amid U.S. Sexual Assault Probe. ","label":[[40,44,"GPE"]]}
{"text":"Bloomberg's Advice For Success: Take As Few Bathroom Breaks As Possible. New York Mayor Michael Bloomberg said on his weekly radio show Friday morning that one of the keys to his success was essentially","label":[[0,9,"ORG"],[12,71,"ORG"],[73,81,"GPE"],[88,105,"PERSON"],[118,124,"DATE"],[136,142,"DATE"],[143,150,"TIME"],[156,159,"CARDINAL"]]}
{"text":"10 Lies We Tell Ourselves Before We Have Kids. I'm going to let them cry it out... for five minutes until I go back in begging them to go back to sleep while considering climbing into the crib with them.","label":[[0,2,"CARDINAL"],[87,99,"TIME"]]}
{"text":"Paul Ryan Renews Call To Suspend Hillary Clinton's Classified Briefings. Yup, Republicans are making the most of this.","label":[[0,24,"PERSON"],[33,50,"PERSON"],[51,71,"ORG"],[78,89,"NORP"]]}
{"text":"The World's Oldest Tree Looks Very Familiar. At just 16 feet tall, Old Tjikko is tiny compared to its 180-foot siblings on the Fulufjället Mountain in Sweden, but it has the proud stature of a great redwood -- standing a little straighter as the oldest single-stemmed clonal tree in the world.","label":[[48,60,"QUANTITY"],[102,110,"QUANTITY"],[123,147,"LOC"],[151,157,"GPE"]]}
{"text":"The Gift That Can't Be Gift Wrapped. Never could I have imagined the huge differences between life in Madagascar and life in England. In the same way that I never really thought twice about not having clean water and a toilet while growing up; people in London don't think twice about having it. That is just the way it is. Imagine, though, if poor communities had that same gift, that same opportunity!","label":[[0,13,"PERSON"],[23,35,"PERSON"],[102,112,"GPE"],[125,132,"GPE"],[254,260,"GPE"]]}
{"text":"Chefs We Love: Alice Waters. The Art of Simple Food In The Green Kitchen 40 Years of Chez Panisse: The Power of Gathering Chez Panisse Cafe Cookbook Chez","label":[[15,27,"PERSON"],[29,51,"WORK_OF_ART"],[85,97,"ORG"],[99,153,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"Passover Recipes Featuring All The Matzo, Charoset And Gefilte Fish You Need. We love to treat Passover as a sort of springtime Thanksgiving, with plenty of leftovers.","label":[[35,40,"PERSON"],[128,140,"DATE"]]}
{"text":"The U.S. Needs New Strategies To Fight Zika Mosquitos. The Aedes aegypti has been dubbed \"the cockroach of mosquitoes,\" because it's so hard to kill.","label":[[4,8,"GPE"]]}
{"text":"HPV Rates Are Going Way Down For Young Women, Study Says. Thanks to the vaccine introduced a decade ago, there has been a 64 percent decrease in human papillomavirus for older teens.","label":[[91,103,"DATE"],[122,132,"PERCENT"]]}
{"text":"Donald Trump's Lawyer Apologizes For 'Inarticulate Comment' About Spousal Rape. He also threatened The Daily Beast for publishing the comment in the first place.","label":[[0,14,"PERSON"],[66,78,"PERSON"],[99,114,"ORG"],[149,154,"ORDINAL"]]}
{"text":"Wheelchair Wisdom: 'Dance With Me!'. Living with MS, a progressive illness, has forced me to accept sudden changes in life that are not always easy or pleasant to deal with. Accepting and loving myself -- overcoming fear, embarrassment, and self-consciousness -- was a significant milestone for me.","label":[[0,17,"PERSON"],[49,51,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"12 Foods Nutritionists Won't Eat. Everyone splurges once in a while, even nutritionists. But these healthy eaters won't touch certain foods.","label":[[0,2,"CARDINAL"]]}
{"text":"The Summer's Dumbest Video Game Is Also Kind Of My Favorite. Mario and Sonic go to Rio, baby!","label":[[71,76,"ORG"],[83,86,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"The Best Root Beer: A HuffPost Deathmatch. Vote now in the final round! It's Stewart's vs. IBC.","label":[[0,18,"PERSON"],[20,41,"WORK_OF_ART"],[77,84,"PERSON"],[91,94,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"The BBC Is Filming \"Songs Of Praise\" At Migrant Church In Calais And Some People Are Furious. TV crews plan to broadcast footage from a migrant camp in Calais, France full of people hoping to reach Britain.","label":[[4,7,"ORG"],[40,64,"ORG"],[152,158,"GPE"],[160,166,"GPE"],[198,205,"GPE"]]}
{"text":"Introverts And Extroverts Can Be Ideal Teammates -- Moving Beyond Perceptions. By: Rita Balian Allen, Rita B. Allen Associates, May 2017 Executive Coach, Author, Trainer, Speaker, Leadership Development","label":[[83,100,"PERSON"],[102,126,"PERSON"],[128,136,"DATE"],[154,160,"GPE"],[162,169,"GPE"]]}
{"text":"Beauty Routine: What Is in Martha Stewart's Vanity. Martha Stewart is a face mask lover and, in this, she is woman after my own heart. I don't use a face mask every day (as Martha seems to), but several times a week and my favorite is Royal Nectar's Bee Venom Mask.","label":[[0,14,"PERSON"],[27,43,"PERSON"],[52,66,"PERSON"],[159,168,"DATE"],[173,179,"PERSON"],[235,249,"ORG"],[250,264,"PRODUCT"]]}
{"text":"Finding My Community at Stupid Cancer's OMG Summit for Young Adults. From the get go, I've been treated at a pediatric hospital, on pediatric protocols, and may, by age, be considered pediatric -- but I am far from it. For once, I was in a room with survivors that got me.","label":[[24,39,"ORG"],[40,67,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"U.S.: Russia Sent Tanks, Rocket Launchers To Rebels In Ukraine. ","label":[[0,4,"GPE"],[6,12,"GPE"],[25,41,"PERSON"],[55,62,"GPE"]]}
{"text":"Kermit The Frog Covering Shaggy's 2000s Classic 'It Wasn't Me' Is Comedy Gold. \"But she caught me on the counter...\"","label":[[0,33,"ORG"],[40,47,"PRODUCT"]]}
{"text":"Kind Snacks Is Fighting For The Right To Call Nuts 'Healthy'. We know more about health than we did in the '90s. Why haven’t nutrition labels caught up?","label":[[107,111,"DATE"]]}
{"text":"Me and My Shadow: Six Years Later. It's very difficult to describe a disease and the overall toll it takes as in my case of stage IV breast cancer.","label":[[10,16,"PRODUCT"],[18,33,"DATE"],[130,132,"GPE"]]}
{"text":"America Is Sinking, And Only The People Can Rescue It. Here's How.. The ship is taking on water, systems are in disarray and communications are down.","label":[[0,7,"GPE"]]}
{"text":"Helen Fisher's GPS Guide For When You Can't Stop Worrying. Your troubles are temporary.","label":[[0,14,"PERSON"],[15,57,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"NYT: White House Vetting Iowa Judge For Supreme Court Seat. WASHINGTON — The White House is vetting Jane L. Kelly, a career public defender turned federal appellate judge, as a potential","label":[[5,16,"ORG"],[40,58,"ORG"],[60,70,"GPE"],[73,88,"ORG"],[100,113,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"\"We\" vs. \"Me\" Couples. The \"me\" couple operates as two distinct people who happen to be in a relationship. The \"we\" couples are unquestionably a team. You see it in their body language and especially in their speech.","label":[[10,21,"WORK_OF_ART"],[51,54,"CARDINAL"]]}
{"text":"9 Animals That May Or May Not Know The Super Bowl 48 Winner. The competition is so fierce that it seems more animals are placing their bets this year, too. Though we're not totally sure","label":[[0,1,"CARDINAL"],[15,18,"DATE"],[140,149,"DATE"]]}
{"text":"Ukraine Says Unrest Planned And Financed From Abroad. ","label":[[0,7,"GPE"]]}
{"text":"Ingenious Compromise: Reason for Hope. Does a sharply divided America necessarily mean that no meaningful legislation can emerge from our political leaders on both sides of the aisle?  I don't think so! What many people describe as the greatest political agreement in the history of the world came out of a deeply divided America -- the US Constitution.","label":[[62,69,"GPE"],[322,329,"GPE"],[333,352,"LAW"]]}
{"text":"Jenni Rhodes, 81, Is Already Our New Favorite Model (PHOTOS). Luckily, Rhodes is represented by Close Models, so she's already had a multitude of modeling gigs from fashion spreads to","label":[[0,12,"ORG"],[14,16,"DATE"]]}
{"text":"Madonna Gets A Spanking From Jessica Chastain On Stage In Prague. Girls gone wild.","label":[[0,28,"PERSON"],[58,64,"GPE"]]}
{"text":"THIS Is How to Transform Your Relationship With Your Daughter. There's no time like the present to begin transforming your relationship with your daughter. Communication is the key and we're laying the foundation today for a more fulfilling tomorrow. It's easy to accomplish and a great way to kick off the summer.","label":[[213,218,"DATE"],[303,313,"DATE"]]}
{"text":"'Zero Hope For Denuclearizing North Korea,' China Expert Says. Trump's designation of North Korea as a state sponsor of terrorism \"could greatly undermine\" a diplomatic solution.","label":[[30,41,"GPE"],[44,49,"GPE"],[63,68,"ORG"],[86,97,"GPE"]]}
{"text":"Sassy and Sophisticated: Diablo Ballet All Grown Up at 20. After 20 years of charming East Bay audiences, Walnut Creek-based Diablo Ballet tipped its hat to the past with an anniversary program that segued movingly from film clips of past performances to live performance of the same pieces, but also nodded vigorously to the future with a brand new work by resident choreographer Robert Dekkers.","label":[[0,5,"ORG"],[10,23,"ORG"],[55,57,"CARDINAL"],[65,73,"DATE"],[86,94,"LOC"],[106,118,"GPE"],[125,138,"ORG"],[381,395,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"Jimmy Fallon Proves He Could Be The Next Michael Strahan With Hilarious 'Live' Audition. Kelly Ripa confirmed they have good chemistry!","label":[[0,19,"PERSON"],[41,56,"PERSON"],[89,99,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"In Conversation With Saul Williams. Alright, so we know Saul is full of magic, but how do we go beyond the quotes and a performance (his performances are one of a kind experience and highly recommended) and get in conversation with Saul?","label":[[21,34,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"Donald Trump Is Winning At Being The Butt Of Late-Night TV Jokes. He did promise he'd win at everything.","label":[[0,12,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"Scientists Map Acorn Worm DNA, And Learn A Lot About Humans In The Process. Turns out we share DNA with a lot of unexpected critters -- and bananas.","label":[[11,25,"PERSON"],[35,59,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"College Relations: Boston's Brains Behind the Olympics. For most of American history, America's colleges and universities have sat in isolated splendor as \"cities upon a hill\" separated by gates and green lawns from the towns in which they lived. In these circumstances, the college relied on its non-profit status as an educator and saw little value in extending its relationships very deep into the neighborhoods that surrounded it.","label":[[19,25,"GPE"],[46,54,"EVENT"],[68,76,"NORP"],[86,93,"GPE"]]}
{"text":"Why Hasn't A Woman Run The New York Times Styles Section In Decades?. The paper's latest hire, Choire Sicha, draws high praise. But inescapably gendered criticisms have always dogged the section.","label":[[23,41,"ORG"],[95,107,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"Marlena Titian's GPS Guide On Being Mindful In The Face Of Stress. Keep these mantras in mind when you're overwhelmed.","label":[[0,16,"ORG"],[17,26,"ORG"],[47,65,"WORK_OF_ART"]]}
{"text":"From Ball Turret Gunner To Guerilla Fighter. Clem Dowler’s Extraordinary Journey Fighting Alongside the Office of Strategic Services in Occupied France: Clement “Clem","label":[[5,23,"PERSON"],[100,132,"ORG"],[136,151,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"The State of Masculinity in America and the One Film Every Man Must See. ","label":[[0,35,"ORG"],[40,52,"EVENT"]]}
{"text":"Why Latinos Should Speak Up for Black Lives. It's time that we, as Latinos, boldly speak out in support of justice.  If we are to truly deal with racism in America impacting Latinos, we need to understand what is happening right now with Black America.","label":[[32,43,"ORG"],[67,74,"PERSON"],[156,163,"GPE"],[174,181,"PERSON"],[238,251,"LOC"]]}
{"text":"Lindsey Vonn Injury: Skier Tears ACL And MCL In Austria. Champion skier Lindsey Vonn is in the hospital following a Tuesday night crash during the opening day of the women's Super","label":[[0,19,"PERSON"],[21,36,"PERSON"],[41,44,"ORG"],[48,55,"GPE"],[72,84,"PERSON"],[116,123,"DATE"],[124,129,"TIME"],[143,158,"DATE"]]}
{"text":"Uber Driver Denies Ride To Woman In Labor, Still Charges $13. The charge was for the time he spent with her and her husband.","label":[[58,60,"MONEY"]]}
{"text":"Life on a Volcanic Island. Skimming across the Tyrrhenian sea, one can see the Gran Cratere of Vulcano in the distance. Arriving in this volcanic island was like approaching Jurassic Park, with its steep hills of vines and trees, deserted coastline and smoking crater.","label":[[10,25,"LOC"],[47,57,"NORP"],[75,102,"WORK_OF_ART"],[174,187,"GPE"]]}
{"text":"How Tim Pawlenty Blew It On The Biggest Stage Of His Career. The anatomy of a debate flub.","label":[[28,52,"WORK_OF_ART"]]}
{"text":"10 Unexpected Ways To Meditate Every Day. Ready to get Zen? Meditation can do way more than people think -- and it's not just for hippies. Practicing meditation regularly","label":[[0,2,"CARDINAL"]]}
{"text":"Quarter Of World's Land Will Be Permanently Drier If Paris Climate Goals Not Met: Study. Countries need to work to prevent the Earth's temperature from rising more than 1.5 degrees.","label":[[0,49,"ORG"],[53,58,"GPE"],[127,132,"LOC"],[159,172,"CARDINAL"]]}
{"text":"Bucket List For Parents: 'Before They Leave Me' Lists. Read through and then tell us: what would be on your list? Use the comments or tweet your answers to @HuffPostParents with","label":[[0,11,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"Minor Explosion Rattles IMF Headquarters In Paris. One person was slightly injured.","label":[[44,49,"GPE"],[51,54,"CARDINAL"]]}
{"text":"The Art of Receiving Is Different From the Act of Taking. I think we could all learn something significant from dogs regarding the nature of not just giving, but receiving. There seems to sufficient conversation around the need to be a good giver, and appropriately so, but there is little talk about the other end of the stick.","label":[[0,56,"WORK_OF_ART"]]}
{"text":"NHL Week In Review: Kings, Blackhawks Follow Different Paths In First Week Of Season. MVP goaltender Jonathan Quick let up 12 goals in his first four games after returning from offseason back surgery. Whatever","label":[[0,8,"ORG"],[27,60,"PERSON"],[86,89,"ORG"],[101,115,"PERSON"],[123,125,"CARDINAL"],[139,144,"ORDINAL"],[145,149,"CARDINAL"]]}
{"text":"Huge Fire Burns Dubai's Torch Tower, One Of The World's Tallest. Authorities said the tower had been evacuated and no injuries were reported.","label":[[0,23,"ORG"],[24,35,"FAC"],[37,40,"CARDINAL"]]}
{"text":"An Oscar-Themed Open Letter to Demi Moore. Demi... let's just look at that post-dumped reinvention of Ellen's, shall we? And take heed.","label":[[3,27,"ORG"],[31,41,"GPE"],[102,107,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"We're Already Creating Our Spring Wish Lists After Seeing This Week's Cheap Celeb Finds. After more than a month of various Fashion Weeks and countless award shows, we've laid our eyes on one too many items of","label":[[6,57,"WORK_OF_ART"],[63,67,"DATE"],[70,87,"ORG"],[95,112,"DATE"],[124,137,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"Watch Britney Spears Dance In A Bikini 'Til The World Ends. It's her prerogative.","label":[[40,58,"WORK_OF_ART"]]}
{"text":"Managing Graduation Trepidation: 3 Techniques to Help New Graduates Interview Confidently. It is an unfortunate coincidence that this year's graduates must experience both elation and trepidation. While they rightfully deserve to bask in their academic accomplishments and celebrate, these young men and women must also confront one of our biggest fears as they prepare to interview for jobs or graduate school.","label":[[33,34,"CARDINAL"],[49,77,"ORG"],[134,138,"DATE"]]}
{"text":"13 Things That Will Make You Panic When You Enter Your Late 20s. When the f*cking f*ck did we all get so old?","label":[[0,2,"CARDINAL"],[55,63,"DATE"]]}
{"text":"Long-Beaked Echidna Specimen Suggests Egg-Laying Mammal Isn't Extinct In Australia After All. Follow LiveScience on Twitter@livescience. We're also on Facebook &Google+.  Monotremes, which include bizarre little mammals","label":[[151,168,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"Businesses and Environmental Groups Call on President Obama to Create Clean 'Power India' Initiative. A \"Power India\" initiative would coordinate bilateral support from agencies such as the Overseas Private Investment Corporation (OPIC), U.S. Export-Import Bank, and USAID, with the goal of unlocking much needed support for clean energy projects and catalyzing the expansion of beyond-the-grid solar markets to help alleviate energy poverty.","label":[[54,59,"PERSON"],[186,229,"ORG"],[238,261,"ORG"],[267,272,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"Real Weddings: Couples Who Got Married This Weekend. This weekend, our readers attended weddings around the globe, from the U.S. to the U.K. to Nigeria. Click through the slideshow","label":[[39,51,"DATE"],[53,65,"DATE"],[124,128,"GPE"],[136,140,"GPE"],[144,151,"GPE"]]}
{"text":"North Korean Defectors Show Signs Of Possible Radiation Exposure. North Koreans who live near the country's nuclear test site appear to be paying a heavy price.","label":[[0,12,"NORP"],[66,79,"NORP"]]}
{"text":"Dog Dies On United Flight After Passenger Forced To Put Carrier In Overhead Bin. The airlines says it takes \"full responsibility for this tragedy.\"","label":[[67,79,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"Trump Officially Declares Opioid Crisis An Emergency 2 Months After Saying He Would. The president's declaration of a public health emergency falls short of previous indications that he'd declare a national emergency.","label":[[0,39,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"Mike Pence: The Birther Issue Is Over. For over five years, his running mate Donald Trump fueled racist conspiracies that Obama was not born in the U.S.","label":[[0,10,"PERSON"],[43,58,"DATE"],[77,89,"PERSON"],[122,127,"PERSON"],[148,152,"GPE"]]}
{"text":"Congress Ties Controversial Cybersecurity Bill To Key Spending Package. And critics are not happy about it.","label":[[0,70,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"Funny RSVP Card Shows Off Couple's Sense Of Humor (PHOTO). A typical wedding RSVP card usually gives guests the option to check one of two boxes: either \"happily accept\" or \"regretfully","label":[[128,131,"CARDINAL"],[135,138,"CARDINAL"]]}
{"text":"8 Ways To Achieve More While Working Less. ","label":[[0,1,"CARDINAL"]]}
{"text":"FBI: Suspected Islamic State Backer Held For New York Attack Plot. \"The FBI remains concerned about people overseas who use the Internet to inspire people in the United States to commit acts of violence where they live.\"","label":[[0,3,"ORG"],[45,65,"GPE"],[72,75,"ORG"],[158,175,"GPE"]]}
{"text":"Extreme Weather Photos Of The Week. Though the Sierra Nevada received some snowfall this past week, California's drought conditions continued to worsen and snowpack","label":[[0,22,"PERSON"],[26,34,"DATE"],[43,60,"ORG"],[84,98,"DATE"],[100,110,"GPE"]]}
{"text":"FABRICATIONS: 14 Fashion Designers Who Are Queering The Fashion Industry. An examination of how the fashion world intersects with queerness and evolving mainstream conceptions of gender.","label":[[14,16,"CARDINAL"]]}
{"text":"Why We Called for a Boycott of the White House Iftar. President Obama used a religious event to make a political statement -- one that was simultaneously an insult to the entire Muslim- and Arab-American community.","label":[[31,52,"ORG"],[64,69,"PERSON"],[190,203,"NORP"]]}
{"text":"Winning Powerball Numbers May 18: 22, 10, 13, 14, 52 And 11. The previous Powerball jackpot record was set in November 2012, when two winning tickets split a prize of $587.5 million","label":[[26,33,"DATE"],[34,36,"CARDINAL"],[38,40,"DATE"],[42,44,"DATE"],[46,48,"DATE"],[50,52,"DATE"],[110,123,"DATE"],[130,133,"CARDINAL"],[167,181,"MONEY"]]}
{"text":"New Witness Account Undermines Mexican Government Narrative Of Missing Students. ","label":[[0,79,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"Mountain Lion Tracked By Scientists Is Found Dead Near Malibu Road. The loss of the famed cougar is one more reason for a California wildlife corridor to protect the big cats, animal advocates say.","label":[[0,66,"ORG"],[100,103,"CARDINAL"],[122,132,"GPE"]]}
{"text":"What the Secret Service Needs to Do Now. ","label":[[5,29,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"Here's Why Tom Hanks Keeps Buying Coffee Machines For The White House Press Corps. \"It's as simple as that.\"","label":[[11,20,"PERSON"],[54,81,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"Bugarach, French Hamlet, Attracts Believers As Mayan Apocalypse Looms (PHOTOS). \"This is the 183rd end-of-the-world prophecy since antiquity,\" Bugarach Mayor Pierre Delord told The Guardian. \"I can't take","label":[[0,8,"GPE"],[10,16,"NORP"],[93,98,"ORDINAL"],[143,151,"PERSON"],[158,171,"PERSON"],[181,189,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"Dear Kate: A Little Girl Answers Your Questions About Autism. Dear Concerned, Rather than looking critically at the number of diagnoses surrounding us, use that analytical mind of yours and do some serious autism research for me.","label":[[5,9,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"America Added 255,000 Jobs In July. This marks the second straight month of strong growth.","label":[[0,29,"ORG"],[30,34,"DATE"],[47,72,"DATE"]]}
{"text":"Volunteering Linked With Lower Risk Of High Blood Pressure. The study, published in the journal Psychology and Aging, included 1,164 adults between ages 51 and 91, who all had normal","label":[[127,132,"CARDINAL"],[140,162,"DATE"]]}
{"text":"CityLove Goes to Boise, Idaho. The future for this neighborhood will certainly be complicated and something the National Trust will be monitoring with great","label":[[17,22,"GPE"],[24,29,"GPE"],[108,126,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"Demystifying SEO for Your CEO. Once a small business CEO recognizes they can easily master the key elements of Google -- and even turn Google into their best salesperson -- they're empowered to do even more.","label":[[135,141,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"Why This Priest Walked Hundreds Of Miles To Protest Donald Trump. Jose Landaverde and other Latino demonstrators faced a slew of racist threats on their journey to Ohio.","label":[[52,64,"PERSON"],[66,81,"PERSON"],[92,98,"PERSON"],[164,168,"GPE"]]}
{"text":"Actually, Burger King Has Been Trying To Dodge Taxes For Years. ","label":[[10,37,"ORG"],[41,46,"ORG"],[57,62,"DATE"]]}
{"text":"\"Troubled\" Moses or Traumatic Origins of the Bible?. We have no way to ascertain whether Moses personally suffered from trauma. He lived long before history was written down in Israel and the stories about him are shrouded in centuries of later tradition.","label":[[45,50,"WORK_OF_ART"],[177,183,"GPE"],[226,235,"DATE"]]}
{"text":"The Political Theology Of Trumpian Evangelicalism. God sides with the powerful.","label":[[0,49,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"Flash Mob Proposal: 'Blob' Dances To Bruno Mars, Pops The Question (VIDEO). We've all seen flash mob marriage proposals. But this is the first time we've heard of a flash \"blob\" proposal. As Kelly","label":[[0,21,"PERSON"],[21,25,"PERSON"],[137,142,"ORDINAL"],[191,196,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"WATCH: Nebraska's Wild, Last-Minute Touchdown Was 58 Yards Of Game-Winning Power. ","label":[[7,15,"GPE"],[18,22,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"Skyler Berman's First Day Of School Outfit Blows Yours Out Of The Water (PHOTO). Just think: By fifth grade, he'll be rocking three-piece suits... with cufflinks. Thought your shiny new Chucks and Jansport","label":[[7,13,"PERSON"],[16,71,"DATE"],[96,101,"ORDINAL"],[126,131,"CARDINAL"],[186,192,"PERSON"],[197,205,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"How to Celebrate Elvis Week. On August 16, 1977, Elvis Presley died at Graceland, his sanctuary and estate in Memphis, Tennessee. He was just 42 years old. The news sent a wave of shock and sadness as the world mourned the man who transformed how we listen to music and so much more.","label":[[7,27,"PERSON"],[32,47,"DATE"],[49,62,"PERSON"],[71,80,"PERSON"],[110,117,"GPE"],[119,128,"GPE"],[142,154,"DATE"]]}
{"text":"Twitter Hilariously Reacts To Trump’s Bad Susan B. Anthony Joke. \"Have you heard of Susan B. Anthony? I’m shocked.”","label":[[0,26,"ORG"],[42,63,"PERSON"],[84,100,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"The Best Tips And Products For Dealing With 'Allergy Face' This Season. Cover up the rest: A hard-working concealer will get you far on mornings like these. To battle redness, look for formulas","label":[[0,13,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"10 Comics That Depict Your Darkest Feelings With Freakish Accuracy. The best ideas usually come while I'm occupied with something else. Mindless tasks are the best: puttering around on my lunch","label":[[0,2,"CARDINAL"],[49,66,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"Ob\/Gyns, Infertility Doctors: Toxic Chemicals Harm Mom, Dad And Baby. The powerful new statement affirms that toxic chemicals in the environment are harming our reproductive health. They are harming our fetuses and babies, and they are harming our health as women, men, mothers and fathers.","label":[[0,7,"ORG"],[9,54,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"Seeking spheres of influence, Russia, China imitate America. ","label":[[30,36,"GPE"],[38,43,"GPE"],[52,59,"GPE"]]}
{"text":"Taylor Swift Was 'The Happiest Maid Of Honor Ever' At Her Best Friend's Wedding. \"I met her when I was 10 days old, and him in kindergarten.\"","label":[[0,18,"PERSON"],[18,50,"WORK_OF_ART"],[103,114,"DATE"]]}
{"text":"Asteroid 1998 QE2 To Give Earth A Close Shave On May 31 (VIDEO). In fact, in 2016, the agency plans to send a robotic probe to one of the most potentially hazardous asteroids. And NASA recently","label":[[49,55,"DATE"],[77,81,"DATE"],[127,130,"CARDINAL"],[180,184,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"Homeland Security Secretary Thinks Marijuana Is 'Not A Factor In The Drug War'. And the solution to drug abuse \"is not arresting a lot of users,\" John Kelly said.","label":[[28,44,"PERSON"],[146,156,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"Donald W. Bush?. It seems that Bush is being forgotten, possibly on the grounds that no former president could look bad with Donald Trump in the White House.","label":[[0,14,"PERSON"],[31,35,"PERSON"],[125,137,"PERSON"],[141,156,"FAC"]]}
{"text":"Firebrand Politician Looks Set To Clinch Philippine Presidency. Rodrigo Duterte's truculent defiance of political tradition has drawn comparisons with U.S. Republican presidential candidate Donald Trump, as have his references to his libido.","label":[[41,51,"NORP"],[64,79,"PERSON"],[151,155,"GPE"],[156,166,"NORP"],[190,202,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"This Stylish Kid Will Teach You How To Wear A Suit. Too. Much. Cuteness.","label":[[0,12,"PERSON"],[63,71,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"Trump Talked About Banning Lobbyists, Now He Might Put Them In Charge. Reports say influence-peddlers Corey Lewandowski and David Urban could join the White House staff.","label":[[0,12,"PERSON"],[102,119,"PERSON"],[124,135,"PERSON"],[151,162,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"Eclipse 2017: How A Tiny Town Braces For Blackout. Cashiers, North Carolina, population 3,500, could be overrun with 30,000 to 100,000 starry-eyed tourists.","label":[[61,75,"GPE"],[88,93,"CARDINAL"],[117,123,"CARDINAL"],[127,134,"CARDINAL"]]}
{"text":"Robin Williams' Kids Ask That We Fill The World Up With Laughter Again. ","label":[[0,15,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"Memorial Day Sales 2012: Home Decor And Outdoor Furniture Sales At Macy's, Sears, Home Depot And More (PHOTOS). This Memorial Day, we honor the courageous men and women who serve or have served our country. Thanks to them, we feel protected","label":[[25,35,"ORG"],[67,71,"ORG"],[75,109,"ORG"],[112,129,"EVENT"]]}
{"text":"Bristol Palin Gives Birth To Her Second Child. Meet Sailor Grace!","label":[[0,13,"ORG"],[20,25,"PERSON"],[33,39,"ORDINAL"]]}
{"text":"What's Leaving Netflix In February 2017?. Aw, pooh.","label":[[7,22,"PERSON"],[26,39,"DATE"]]}
{"text":"Heart Drugs: Too Many Medication Types Are Compromising Health, Doctors Say. Beta-blockers are absolutely necessary for some patients, said Dr. Sripal Bangalore, a cardiologist at New York University","label":[[144,160,"PERSON"],[180,199,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"NYC Nightlife Icons Transform James. St. James. ","label":[[0,35,"ORG"],[37,46,"GPE"]]}
{"text":"Every Woman Counts: Gender Budgeting In G7 Countries. How national budgets can be used more actively as a tool to support gender equality.","label":[[20,36,"PERSON"],[40,52,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"In 100 Days, Trump Has Found 29 Ways To Screw Regular Americans. This is populism?","label":[[3,11,"DATE"],[13,22,"ORG"],[29,31,"CARDINAL"],[46,63,"NORP"]]}
{"text":"Ted Cruz Blasts Big Money In Politics. But his solution is more big money in politics.","label":[[0,8,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"The World Government Summit and the Arabs' Heartache. ","label":[[0,27,"ORG"],[36,41,"NORP"]]}
{"text":"'Dirty Dancing' Was A Safe-Abortion Champion Wrapped In A Rom-Com Bow. Screenwriter Eleanor Bergstein reflects on her hit script 30 years later.","label":[[71,101,"PERSON"],[129,143,"DATE"]]}
{"text":"Radiation Technique For Knockoffs May Be The Coolest Way To Spot A Fake. However, as Salon notes, certain counterfeits could still fool the system -- but only if they were made with the same type","label":[[85,90,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"Cavaliers' Championship Window Is Quickly Closing. LeBron continues to dazzle, but his teammates are floundering.","label":[[51,57,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"Heidi Klum As A Young Punk And More Tweets Of The Week (PHOTOS). We love when celebrities post throwback photos of themselves as kids, and Heidi Klum always posts the best ones. This week","label":[[0,10,"PERSON"],[46,54,"DATE"],[139,149,"PERSON"],[178,187,"DATE"]]}
{"text":"Americans Call Clinton, Trump The Worst Nominees In 40 Years. More than a third of voters say they don't like either option.","label":[[0,9,"NORP"],[52,60,"DATE"],[62,79,"CARDINAL"]]}
{"text":"U.S. Killed Up To 116 Civilians In Drone Strikes Outside War Zones, White House Says. The total is far lower than estimates by non-governmental organizations.","label":[[0,4,"GPE"],[18,21,"CARDINAL"],[68,79,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"Worried About Donald Trump, Asylum Seekers Walk Cold Road To Canada. “The election and inauguration of Mr. Trump appears to be the final reason for those who came mostly last month.”","label":[[14,26,"PERSON"],[61,67,"GPE"],[107,112,"PERSON"],[170,180,"DATE"]]}
{"text":"NFL Player Stedman Bailey In Critical Condition After Shooting. Bailey will undergo surgery after reportedly being shot in the head twice.","label":[[0,3,"ORG"],[11,25,"PERSON"],[64,70,"GPE"]]}
{"text":"Experimental Treatment For Antibiotic-Resistant UTIs Succeeds In Trial. An estimated 2 million patients each year in the United States contract drug-resistant infections, the company said, citing","label":[[27,70,"ORG"],[72,94,"CARDINAL"],[104,113,"DATE"],[117,134,"GPE"]]}
{"text":"HuffPost Live: Heal The West (VIDEO). Columbia University has just opened the Spirituality & Mind-Body Institute, an innovative program that aims to bring a spiritual","label":[[38,57,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"Black Poet Explains Painful Reality Of Police Violence To His 4-Year-Old Nephew. The harsh truth that every black child eventually has to hear.","label":[[62,79,"DATE"]]}
{"text":"Medical Devices Need To Be Protected Against Cyber Threats: FDA. The risk of breaches has grown as devices have become increasingly interconnected, via the Internet, hospital networks, other","label":[[60,63,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"Huckabee Compares Gavin Newsom To Kentucky Clerk, Sparks Twitter War. California Lieutenant Governor Gavin Newsom (D) and GOP presidential candidate Mike Huckabee sparred on Twitter on Sunday","label":[[18,30,"PERSON"],[34,48,"PERSON"],[50,68,"WORK_OF_ART"],[70,80,"GPE"],[101,113,"PERSON"],[122,125,"ORG"],[149,162,"PERSON"],[174,181,"WORK_OF_ART"],[185,191,"DATE"]]}
{"text":"Embarrassing Dads: Survey Finds 60% Of Kids Think Dads Are 'Lame'. It is a universal truth that parents will, at some point or another, embarrass their children. But a recent online survey","label":[[32,35,"PERCENT"]]}
{"text":"Hillary Rodham Clinton Makes It Official: She Is Running. Over the next months, they will hear her platform and policy initiatives and realize that she is the right person to be president. Hillary will run a campaign that will reach out across party lines in the same way she did when she was in the Senate.","label":[[0,28,"PERSON"],[63,78,"DATE"],[189,196,"PERSON"],[300,306,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"Jan. 9, 2012 News Update. The 150th anniversary of the Emancipation Proclamation observed. Some Southerners still think it was a mistake. New Congress","label":[[0,24,"DATE"],[30,35,"ORDINAL"],[51,80,"FAC"],[96,107,"NORP"],[138,150,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"Trump First Offered Jerry Falwell, Jr. U.S. Secretary Of Education Job. The Associated Press reported the following on November 26, 2016: RICHMOND, Va. (AP) — Liberty University President Jerry","label":[[0,11,"ORG"],[20,33,"PERSON"],[39,43,"GPE"],[57,66,"ORG"],[72,92,"ORG"],[119,136,"DATE"],[138,146,"GPE"],[148,151,"GPE"],[153,155,"ORG"],[159,177,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"Rex Tillerson Says Transgender People Should Not Be Discriminated Against. Meanwhile, the Trump administration is pushing anti-trans policies.","label":[[19,37,"PERSON"],[90,95,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"Kim Kardashian, Miley Cyrus Share Sexy Selfies For Interview Magazine September Issue. They're part of the mag's not-so-secret #Instagang.","label":[[0,14,"PERSON"],[16,69,"ORG"],[70,79,"DATE"],[107,110,"ORG"],[128,137,"GPE"]]}
{"text":"Bikinis, Stylish One-Pieces and The 11 Other Best Swimsuits For Your Shape (PHOTOS). Summer is here and while we couldn't be more excited about long weekends at the beach, the thought of getting into a swimsuit","label":[[0,7,"ORG"],[9,27,"ORG"],[36,38,"CARDINAL"],[39,59,"LOC"]]}
{"text":"Rachel Bilson Shops At TJ Maxx In A Denim Jumpsuit, Making Us Love Her Even More. But new photos have surfaced that make our adoration for the former \"O.C.\" star (she's always be Summer to us) grow even","label":[[0,19,"PERSON"],[59,80,"WORK_OF_ART"],[151,155,"GPE"]]}
{"text":"Why I Walked Away From My Six-Figure Job... and the Surprising Results a Decade Later. I'd gotten a job in finance in my early 20s, and the next thing I knew, I was 36 years old and on a career trajectory not of my choosing. Yes, I was succeeding, but at what cost?","label":[[48,70,"LAW"],[118,130,"DATE"],[165,177,"DATE"]]}
{"text":"Full-Page Ad In The New York Times Demands Diversity At Fashion Week. \"Let's move from talk to action.\"","label":[[16,55,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"Understanding the Narcolepsy-Autoimmune Relationship. Both of these studies offer compelling new information about the root causes and mechanisms of this very serious disorder. They also offer the promise of swifter and more accurate diagnoses, and of improvements to treatment.","label":[[14,52,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"Scott Walker Says There Are A 'Handful Of Reasonable, Moderate Followers Of Islam'. There are more than a handful.","label":[[0,12,"PERSON"],[76,81,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"'Real Housewives Of Atlanta' Star Phaedra Parks Says She's 'Open To Love'. \"Real Housewives of Atlanta\" star Phaedra Parks says she's still open to love despite her very public separation from estranged","label":[[20,27,"GPE"],[34,47,"PERSON"],[68,72,"WORK_OF_ART"],[76,102,"WORK_OF_ART"],[109,122,"PERSON"]]}
{"text":"7 Ways to Boost Your Gratitude. Many of us are well versed at juggling dozens of different thoughts in our heads at once. It is tough to feel true gratitude when your attention is divided. Take the time to really focus on the person you are with or event that is happening in the moment.","label":[[71,77,"CARDINAL"]]}
{"text":"30 Days of High-Intensity Interval Training (HIIT). The high-intensity interval training workouts are the fastest way to look lean and mean when the weather demands we get about wearing fewer clothes. The real benefits, however, are mental. Try one of the routines right now -- all you need is 15 minutes and a timer.","label":[[0,7,"DATE"],[294,304,"TIME"]]}
{"text":"Crystal Bridges Exhibition Reveals Curatorial Missteps. Covering over 19,000 square feet of exhibition space, State of the Art: Discovering American Art Now at the Crystal Bridges Museum of American Art in Bentonville, Arkansas is an enormous undertaking that casts a wide net but misses the mark when it comes to the emergence of strong, definitive themes.","label":[[65,88,"QUANTITY"],[160,186,"FAC"],[190,202,"ORG"],[206,217,"GPE"],[219,227,"GPE"]]}
{"text":"The 2016 March Madness Schedule For Saturday And Sunday's Games. Watch live as your brackets bust.","label":[[4,8,"DATE"],[36,63,"DATE"]]}
{"text":"Thousands Of New York Protesters Rally In Solidarity For Baltimore's Freddie Gray. ","label":[[0,9,"CARDINAL"],[57,66,"GPE"],[69,81,"ORG"]]}
{"text":"12 Ways To Get Your Daily Vitamin D. By Ella Quittner Vitamin D is essential for bone health. Recent research suggests it may have other benefits, too, such as","label":[[0,2,"CARDINAL"],[45,63,"PERSON"]]}
